And reverse the spin
on the antiproton...
...and gamma becomes alpha.
Multiplied by a matrix
of negative I comma zero.
And there we have it.
Conclusive proof that
I am absolutely worthless after 9:00.
SPOOKY VOICE:
Sheldon.
Hmm.
(ENERGY CRACKLING)
All right, all right.
I see what's going on.
A little pre-Halloween hijinkery.
(MOANING)
(WOMAN CACKLING)
(CHAIN RATTLING)
A ghostly moan, a rattling of chains,
a witch's cackle.
Trifecta of haunted house clichés.
Instead of "Eek," I say, "Yawn."
SPOOKY VOICE:
Sheldon.
Oh, the walls are dripping blood...
...which looks nothing
like a phenolphthalein indicator...
...exposed to a sodium carbonate
solution.
"See you in hell, Sheldon."
The most frightening thing about that
is the missing comma.
(SCREAMS THEN PANTS)
Okay, heh, all right.
That one was clever.
Skeleton with phosphorous
on a zip line.
Come on out, merry pranksters.
Take a bow.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
- You should've seen your face.
- Yes.
There's nothing quite like the slightly
widened eyes of mildly startled.
Come on, admit it. We got you.
Please. Fright depends on
an element of surprise.
The simple fact is,
because I am much smarter than you...
...and able to anticipate your actions...
...it is highly unlikely that you two rubes
could ever surprise me.
- He's probably right.
- We can't beat him. He's just too smart.
Gentlemen.
(SCREAMS)
(ALL LAUGHING)
Okay, who had money on "faints"?
I had "pee his pants."
Hang on.
Looks like everyone's a winner.
(CHUCKLING)
Oh, watch out, Sheldon.
This little boy Casper
is a gh... Gh... Gh... Ghost!
- Ha-ha-ha.
- Droll.
Eh, not as droll as a grown man
passed out in a puddle of his own urine.
(ALL CHUCKLE)
That was pretty droll.
With a hint of ammonia.
Yes, enjoy your japes, gentlemen.
Think you've poked fun
at a milquetoast academic.
You've forgotten one thing.
I am also a son of the Lone Star State.
I'm Texas through and through.
And we know how
to settle scores down there.
If you doubt me, ask Mexico.
Hot girl, 9 o'clock.
Don't everybody look at once.
What is she doing
in a comic book store?
I don't know. She might be lost.
Doesn't matter. Watch and learn.
- Hi.
That's, um...
It... It... It...
Shut up.
- Are you getting this Next Men?
- Uh, yeah.
It's issue number 21,
first appearance of Hellboy.
I know.
I've been looking for it for years.
- Sorry.
- Hey, if I pretended to hit on you...
...could I distract you enough
to sneak it away?
Yes, but you'd be using
your superpowers for evil.
Damn, I'm forbidden
by my Kryptonian father to do so.
(CHUCKLES)
- I'm Alice.
- Um, Leonard.
You're very cute, Leonard.
Thanks. You too.
You know, go ahead and take it.
No, no, no, I... I did evil.
- Would you be open to a trade?
- Uh, yeah, yeah, sure, I guess.
Okay. Here. This is my number.
- Call me.
- Sorry, palm's a little sweaty.
What's that word?
- Alice.
- Oh, right, your name.
That makes more sense than "penis."
Later.
Did we just see you pick up a girl
in a comic book store?
Because if you did, you get your picture
up there on the Wall of Heroes.
No, I don't think I picked her up.
Besides, I have a girlfriend.
Doesn't matter.
This is the closest anyone's ever come.
You're going on the wall, my friend.
Be sure to check the mail.
How many times are you gonna tell me?
What's with you?
Nothing.
It's not suspicious that I'm fixating.
It's consistent with my personality.
- Right.
- Hey, guys.
More Halloween candy? Didn't you just
buy a bunch of it yesterday?
Oh, yeah, that's gone.
It's a rough month when Halloween
and PMS hit at the same time.
Leonard doesn't have time to chat.
He has to get the mail.
Oh, will you relax? I'll get it in a minute.
- Hey, how was work?
- Open the mail.
(LEONARD SIGHS)
Excuse me.
A couple of circulars,
nothing important.
- What's with him?
- Hang on.
(HORN BLARES)
You might be from Texas,
but I'm from New Jersey.
(HORN BLARES)
Check it out. Jim Lee drew this of me
two years ago at Comic-Con.
- What are you wearing?
- Well, you know, it's Comic-Con.
I'm Lion-O from ThunderCats.
(LAUGHS)
Wow, you must have gotten so laid.
Heh. No, but Jessica Alba
did rub my furry belly.
(LAUGHS)
Wanna see a comic I draw?
You're kidding.
You have your own book?
- Yeah, it's kind of based on my life.
- Ha, ha. Cool.
Oh, wow, look, there's you having sex...
...with a guy in the top half
of a Chewbacca costume.
- Comic-Con?
- You'd think, but no.
You're very talented.
This is really good. Did you do...?
So can I trade you my comic
for the Hellboy?
You can have my car.
Oh, dear.
Oh, dear. Oh, dear. Oh, dear.
Purell, Purell, Purell, Purell.
- Good morning, Sheldon.
- It is, isn't it?
(GASPS)
Oh, bother.
Isn't that just always the way?
You go to staple something
and you're out of staples.
Gosh, I wish I'd known that earlier today
when I was at Staples.
You have a thing of paper clips
right there.
No, no, uh, I need something
more permanent to join these papers.
Say, uh, don't you keep staples
in your top desk drawer?
I don't know, maybe.
Be a lamb and check.
All right.
(GASPS)
Who do we have here?
It's a snake. A terrifying snake.
Oh. Did some bad man put us
in a drawer?
Stop talking like that.
You've been rendered speechless by fear.
Let's go to the biology lab
and find you some nice yummy mice.
I tried to scare an Indian with a snake.
Come on, Cooper.
You're better than this.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
It's open.
- Hey, you got a minute?
- Yeah, sure. Come on in.
- Thanks.
- Want some mac and cheese?
No. Lactose. Gas.
- Glass of wine?
- No. Sulfites. Migraines.
Well, I'd offer you Halloween candy,
but that's gone.
- So, what's up?
- Okay, we used to go out, right?
Oh, my God.
That's where I know you from.
I'm dealing with a situation
and it's kind of about my love life.
So I know that might be weird
for us to talk about...
...but in this area, as you know,
all my other friends are just so stupid.
All right, what's going on?
- So you're okay talking about this?
- Yes.
- Sure it's not weird?
- It's okay.
If you ever wanna talk to me
about a problem in your life with a guy...
...then I... I'd be fine with that.
Okay, good.
There's this one guy I used to date...
...who's about to be force-fed wine
and cheese if he doesn't get to the point.
Okay, uh, here it is.
Is it cheating
if a guy has a girlfriend...?
Yeah, probably.
- Come on.
- I'm sorry, go ahead.
I met this girl and she's great.
We have a lot in common.
- Did you guys do it?
- No. We just made out a little.
Oh, look at you, you bad boy.
- Did you tell her about Priya?
- Uh, I was gonna...
...but there were too many tongues
in my mouth.
That's gross.
Here's the thing. Uh, I... I'm not one
of those guys who sneaks around...
...and sleeps with
more than one woman.
Well, good for you.
The problem is
I wanna be one of those guys.
So sleep with the new girl
and lie to Priya.
Oh, that's not who I am.
All right.
Then break it off with the new girl.
Now, let's not do anything rash.
She's really hot.
If you like this girl so much,
just end things with Priya.
Priya and I are in love.
I think we could get married someday.
You're looking for a way
to sleep with both women...
- ...and have everybody be happy about it.
- Now we're getting somewhere.
What does your gut tell you?
"Go ask Penny.
She'll know what to do."
Hello, Howard.
I've realized that you scaring me
was all in jest.
Allow me to say, job well done.
(ENERGY CRACKLING)
(GRUNTING)
(GASPS)
Perfect.
- What are you doing?
- Science. You wouldn't understand.
Okay, well, see you. I'm going out.
I thought you were leaving
the apartment.
Yeah, me too.
I can't make up my mind.
Are you concerned because the world
is filled with big dogs and bullies?
No, I'm having a moral crisis.
Well, if it's of any help, I've read all
the great moral philosophers...
...including Dr. Seuss.
Oh, what the hell?
I'm supposed to go see that
girl from the comic book store, Alice.
But I don't know if I should, because I'm
going out with Priya, but she's in India.
All right.
So the topic at hand is sexual fidelity.
Probably won't be relying
on Seuss here.
Although One Fish Two Fish
Red Fish Blue Fish...
...might be surprisingly applicable.
- Go on.
- Well, uh, they say at the end of your life...
...you regret the stuff you didn't do
more than the stuff that you did.
And I'm pretty sure Alice is the stuff
I wanna do.
You know, the German philosopher
Friedrich Nietzsche...
...believed that morality
is just a fiction...
...used by the herd of inferior
human beings...
...to hold back the few superior men.
That actually does help.
It's worth noting
that he died of syphilis.
Screw it, I'm going.
On your way home,
will you pick up orange juice?
Do you mind? I'm questioning
a lot of things in my life.
Is one of those things
your fondness for orange juice?
- No.
- Great. Tropicana, no pulp.
(DOOR BELL RINGS)
- Hey, Sheldon.
WOMAN: Who is it?
It's me, Sheldon, Mrs. Wolowitz.
That's not my mom. It's Bernadette.
Really? That's very unsettling.
- Hi, Sheldon.
- Hi.
- What's up?
- It just occurred to me...
...that I never formally congratulated you
on your pending nuptials.
I hopped on the first bus and hightailed
it down here to shake your hand.
Put her there, you old so-and-so.
Well, uh... I'm gonna see you
at work in 12 hours.
Don't you think
it could have waited until then?
Holy smoke,
why didn't I think of that?
You're a better man than I,
Howard Wolowitz.
You put her there, you son of a gun.
Whatever. Heh.
(GRUNTS)
My...
It's...
Oh, my God, Howie!
What did you do?
It was a harmless Halloween prank.
Look.
Howard has a heart condition.
You know that.
Well, I thought he made that up.
Isn't hypochondria a common
idiosyncrasy of Jewish people?
This is adrenaline.
We're gonna inject it into his heart.
- We are?
- You are. I'm not strong enough...
...to get it through his chest plate
and we've only got one shot.
Oh, no, I can't!
Hurry! We're running out of time!
- Okay.
- Just do it!
Oh, God! One, two, three.
Aah!
Trick or treat, bubbeleh.
What?
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
No. You mean this was all a ruse?
Oh, how could I be so stu...?
(ENERGY CRACKLING)
(ALICE MOANING)
Damn it, I can't... I can't do this.
Is it my tongue stud?
If that freaks you out,
you're in for a real surprise later.
(STAMMERS)
No, no, no. I can't do this.
Believe me, I really want to.
- But?
- But I kind of have a girlfriend.
- Are you kidding?
- Uh, you're cool with being friends, right?
Heh. I don't believe this.
Wait, I don't... Which part?
Heh. I'm so stupid.
I thought for once I'd met a good guy...
- ...but you're just another jackass.
- Oh, no, you have it wrong.
No, I was going to be a jackass,
but I stopped myself.
I stayed a good guy,
so I'm gonna pass on the sex.
But you should know,
that's not a comment on your hotness...
...but on my goodness.
That's kind of my superpower.
I'm... I'm like Captain Good Guy.
(SIGHS)
It's okay. Did the right thing.
You idiot!
- Hey, Priya.
- Hey, sweetheart. How's it going?
Uh. Not so good. We have to talk.
Oh. Sounds serious. What's up?
Okay, uh, here it is.
I met this girl and I kissed her
and I feel terrible about it.
But it's done,
it's never gonna happen again...
...and I am so, so sorry.
Leonard, relax. It's okay.
- It is?
- Yeah, these things happen.
They happen to everybody.
Oh, my God, you are amazing.
I mean, heh, I don't deserve you.
What... What do you mean, "everybody"?
Leonard, I didn't know if
I should tell you...
...but I kind of cheated on you too.
Uh, you... "Kind of"?
A couple of weeks ago,
I slept with my ex-boyfriend.
So I guess we both messed up a little.
No, no, I messed up a little.
You messed up a lot.
Well, it's not a competition.
Oh, yeah, it is and you won.
(STAMMERS)
I'm sorry, I have to go.
I don't believe this.
(BOTH SCREAMING)
Buzzinga, punk. Now we're even.