NARRATOR:
Previously on The Big Bang Theory:
My brother...
...he's got a big crush on Bernadette.
You're moving back to India?
What's going on?
(CHUCKLES)
It's not what it looks like.
(DOOR OPENS AND THEN CLOSES)
What does it look like?
It's not what it looks like.
What are you grinding about?
Penny's brain teaser this morning.
She and Koothrappali
emerge from your bedroom.
She is disheveled
and Raj is dressed only in a sheet.
The sole clue:
It's not what it looks like.
Tsk, just let it go, Sheldon.
If I could, I would,
but I can't, so I shan't.
Now...
...knowing Penny, the obvious answer is
they engaged in coitus.
But since that's what it looks like,
we can rule that out.
Let's put on our thinking caps,
shall we?
Raj is from India, a tropical country,
third-world hygiene...
...parasitic infections are common,
such as pinworms.
- Mm-hm.
- The procedure for diagnosing pinworms...
...is to wait until the subject is asleep...
...and the worms crawl out of the rectum
for air.
Yes, just like that.
Penny could have been inspecting
Raj's anal region for parasites.
Oh, boy, that's a true-blue friend.
They slept together, Sherlock.
(HICCUPS)
No, you weren't listening.
She said, "it's not what it looks like."
She lied.
Oh.
Now don't I look silly
sitting here wearing this?
- Hey.
Hey.
Leonard, is it awkward for you...
...knowing one of your dear friends
had sexual intercourse...
...with a woman you used to love
in the very place you lay your head?
No, I'm fine with it.
That sounds like sarcasm.
But I'm gonna disregard it
because I have an agenda. Paintball.
Specifically, the interdepartmental
tournament this weekend.
Now, in order to function better
as a fighting unit...
...I thought we should establish
a chain of command.
Now, it goes without saying
that I would outrank the three of you.
But the question remains,
by how much?
Now, I don't see me
as some four-star general back at HQ...
...riding a desk and playing golf
with the Secretary of Defense.
But I also can't be Sergeant Cooper
because that might lead you...
...to think of me as a regular Joe. This
might take some thought. As you were.
- What the hell is wrong with you?
- How could you do that?
- What is it to you?
- I got his back.
Yeah, right.
You're jealous because...
...I'm Penny's number-two choice
after Leonard.
Hey, if I wasn't engaged to Bernadette,
that totally could have been me.
Please. Sheldon would've
been before you...
...and he might not even
have genitals.
Why do you care so much?
You're dating my sister...
...and Penny and I are in love.
- What, heh?
- What?
Gentlemen, if I may interject.
I've decided my rank will be captain.
If it's good enough for Kirk,
Crunch and Kangaroo...
...it's good enough for me.
- You're not in love with Penny.
- Yes, I am.
The god Kamadeva has shot us
with his flowery arrows of love.
- Who?
- He's the Hindu version of Cupid...
...but way better
because he rides a giant parrot.
Raj, come on, you fall in love
with any girl who smiles at you.
A month ago, you were writing poems
about his fiancée.
I'm sorry, what?
Rubbish. He's talking rubbish.
(MIMICKING RAJESH)
Oh, Bernadette, please play my clarinet
That could have been about anyone.
You have nothing to worry about,
because now I'm the dusky half...
...of Koothrapenny.
For the record, I do have genitals.
They're functional
and aesthetically pleasing.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Oh. Coming.
Yup, that's good.
Wine glasses should have handles.
Keeping accurate track
of your alcohol intake.
Smart idea, considering how trampy
you get when you've had a few.
You heard what I did?
- Well, I heard who you did.
- Ugh.
Oh, my God, I screwed up everything.
I hurt Leonard, I hurt Raj.
I mean, what is wrong with me?
I feel like two totally different people.
Dr. Jekyll and Mrs. Whore.
Don't be so hard on yourself.
- Know the story of Catherine the Great?
- No.
She ruled Russia in the late 1700s, and
one night when she was feeling randy...
...she used an intricate system of pulleys
to have intimate relations with a horse.
I'm sorry,
what does this have to do with me?
She engaged
in inter-species hanky-panky...
...and people still call her great.
I'm sure your reputation can survive
you shagging a little Indian boy.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
You jerk-face!
What did you tell Howard?
You say there's something going on
between us? He thinks there is.
He's completely freaking out!
Please, come in.
What the hell is wrong with you?
You were always so nice to me,
I thought maybe you liked me.
I'm nice to everyone!
- I'm sorry.
- Damn right, you're sorry.
And you tell Howard
there's never been anything between us.
I will. Hey, Bernadette.
- What?
- Do you think I have a shot with Penny?
Of course, you do. You're a cutie pie.
Any girl would be lucky to have you.
You know, I've done this before.
In kindergarten, I was supposed
to marry Jason Sorensen...
...but by the time my class got out there,
he was engaged to Chelsea Himmelfarb.
What did I do? Hung upside down
from the monkey bars...
...let all the boys see my underpants.
You can't blame yourself.
When your pre-frontal cortex fails
to make you happy...
...promiscuity rewards you
with dopamine.
We neurobiologists refer to this
as the skank reflex.
- You know what? Let's get out of here.
- Where are we going?
Somewhere
where no one's seen me naked.
We may have to drive a while.
Subtlety isn't her strong suit, is it?
Oh, can I stay at your place
for a few nights?
Really? A best-friend sleepover? Yay.
Yeah, sure. Yay, heh.
We'll make popcorn, stay up all night,
and I'll teach you my secret language.
(SPEAKING GIBBERISH)
- Sounds great.
- Nope. Sounds:
(SPEAKING GIBBERISH)
- Yeah, I'm gonna go pack a bag.
- No, you're not. You're gonna:
(SPEAKING GIBBERISH)
Do we really have to wear
this camouflage crap to play paintball?
Who said that? Leonard,
I can hear your voice, but I can't see you.
I'm not in the mood, Sheldon.
Oh, there you are.
Leonard, I know you're upset
about recent events...
...and I have someone here to help.
I don't wanna talk to Amy.
Yeah... No, it's not Amy.
Hello, dear.
You called my mother?
Oh, Leonard, is it really necessary
to caption the obvious?
He's been like that
since he was a toddler.
"Look, Mommy, a butterfly."
Maddening.
What's going on?
What do you want?
Sheldon informed me that you're
experiencing an emotional upheaval...
...and I'm here to help.
That's so nice.
And we're back to the obvious.
Now, what's up?
Well, uh...
Okay, um...
I don't wanna get back with Penny.
We tried it, it was crazy, it didn't work.
But I can't deal with the fact
that she slept with my friend, Raj.
And then I find out
that Raj's sister, Priya...
...who I've been going out with,
is moving back to India.
So I'm just completely confused
and alone.
I understand.
- Got any advice?
- Yes. Buck up.
Excuse me,
you're a world-renowned expert...
...in parenting and child development,
and all you've got is "buck up"?
Sorry.
Buck up, sissy pants.
- Thanks, Mother, I feel better.
- If you need any more help...
...my books are available on Amazon.
Logging off.
Ninety-nine...
...100.
It's like a waterfall of liquid gold.
My turn.
(CLEARS THROAT)
(SIGHS)
Don't know what the point of staying
in L.A. is.
I haven't gotten a single acting job
since I moved out here.
The closest I came was last month. I got
a callback for a hemorrhoid commercial.
Oh, I could so see you
being the face of hemorrhoids.
I know, right?
Ugh, maybe I should just move back
to Nebraska.
- No, I can't let you do that.
- Why not?
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
For the first time ever,
I have a thriving social life.
And no pressure,
but it kind of lives and dies with you.
Hi, Amy, can I talk to Penny?
A guest in my trundle bed
and a boy at my door?
I wish I could tell 13-year-old me
it does get better.
- How did you know I was here?
- It's all over her Facebook page.
- I'll take your stuff and clear a drawer.
- All right, thanks.
No problem.
Try and keep it in your pants, okay?
So...
Hi, what's up?
Wondering if you're free Friday.
They're having '80s night at the Greek.
Hall & Oates, Katrina and the Waves,
and three-fifths of Kajagoogoo.
Oh, heh.
- That's really sweet, but the thing is...
- Oh, there's a thing.
Look, honey, I was really drunk
and made a huge mistake last night.
We should have never slept together.
It's what ruins friendships.
You can't ruin a friendship with sex.
That's like trying to ruin ice cream
with chocolate sprinkles.
Come here. Just...
Listen to me. I...
I wanna go back
to the way we were before.
You know, friends.
No sprinkles.
Oh.
- All right.
- Thank you.
(SIGHS)
Well, uh...
(CLEARS THROAT)
...as your friend,
you might like to know that, um...
...we didn't have sex
in the conventional sense.
Oh, God, did you pull
some weird Indian crap on me?
No, no.
After we got undressed
and jumped in bed...
...you asked if I had protection.
- Oh, you did, didn't you?
- Well, of course. I'm always packing.
Anyway, um, I had trouble putting it on...
...and you tried to help, and...
That was all she wrote.
- So we didn't actually...
- I did. It was beautiful.
Oh.
Penny, promise me
you won't tell anybody about this.
- Of course, I won't.
- Oh, good.
(SIGHS)
And, uh, can I tell people that our love
burned too bright and too quickly?
Kind of a Candle in the Wind deal?
- Sure.
- Oh, good.
It fell apart because you're all,
"I wanna have your babies"...
...and I was like:
"I'm too rock 'n' roll to be tied down"?
No.
Can I say I ruined you for white men?
Also no.
- Okay, just the candle thing.
- Yeah.
Cool.
All right.
- Friend.
- Hmm.
- I'll see you around.
- Okay.
Raj, wait.
Thank you for being my friend.
- Penny.
- Mm-hm.
It's getting beautiful again.
All right. This is a Google Earth view
of the field of battle.
- I don't see anything.
- Give it a second to load.
Whenever you're ready, AT&T.
Okay, here we go. This is us, here.
To the south is Professor Loomis
and the Geology Department.
According to their Twitter feed,
they're out of sunblock...
...which means they'll have
to hug the tree line or risk melanoma.
That's our edge. All we have to do
is move quickly over this ridge.
The rock-worshipping, pasty-faced
bastards won't know what hit them.
Let's move out.
Hang on, Sheldon.
How could you not tell me
your sister was moving back to India?
Maybe he was busy
writing clumsy penis metaphors...
...about my fiancée.
Screw you. That was
a beautifully-written penis metaphor.
You know what?
Guys, I'm not in the mood for paintball.
- What do you say we just bag it?
- Fine.
- Sure, whatever.
- But you can't quit.
That's a court-martial offense.
That's punishable by...
You can't quit.
I'm sorry, Sheldon, it's just
not a good time for playing games.
This is a game to you?
Uh, was the Battle of Antietam
a game, huh?
Was the Sack of Rome a game?
Yes, no and no.
Wait.
I just want you all to know
that I forgive you.
This mutiny isn't your fault.
It's mine.
I haven't earned these bars.
Although what I lack in leadership,
I more than make up for in sewing.
Let it go, Sheldon. I'll get you
a Jamba Juice on the way home.
No. Jamba Juice is for heroes.
And that's what we're going to be.
What are you doing?
Following in the footsteps
of Kirk, Crunch and Kangaroo.
Geology isn't a real science.
(AIR RIFLES FIRING)
- Damn those sons of bitches!
LEONARD: Let's get them!
(ALL SHOUTING)
If there's ever a church of Sheldon,
this will be when it started.
Ow!
I'd like to propose a toast
to the man whose noble sacrifice...
...inspired our victory,
Captain Sheldon Cooper.
- Cheers!
- Excuse me, it's Major Sheldon Cooper.
With my last breath, I awarded myself
a battlefield promotion.
It's kind of a big deal.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Hi. You guys have a minute?
- Uh, yeah, sure.
- Okay, um...
(CLEARS THROAT)
Well, I already talked to Raj, but I wanted
to apologize to the rest of you...
...for, you know, everything.
Please, Penny, let me.
(CLEARS THROAT)
We've decided to let our crazy,
wonderful night together...
...be just one
of those memories you have...
...and can call to mind when you're
feeling blue or you're in the shower.
Hey, what you doing, quick draw?
Sorry. Go on.
(PENNY CLEARS THROAT)
Anyways, I wanted you to know that I've
been taking a really hard look at things...
...and come to the conclusion
I have to stop kidding myself.
I suck at acting.
It's time for me
to move back to Nebraska.
- You're leaving?
- Yeah.
What are you gonna do in Nebraska?
I don't know. Maybe teach acting.
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
Sorry. Hold on. Hello?
I hope you're not doing this
because of you and me...
...because I have a girlfriend
and you're a single...
Shh! It's my agent. It's my agent.
You're kidding.
Oh, my gosh. I can't believe it.
Really?
Oh, I'm so excited. Thank you.
Thank you so much. Okay, bye.
I got the hemorrhoid commercial.
I start Monday.
What about Nebraska?
Oh, hell with Nebraska.
I'm gonna be a star.
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
Have you ever thought
of teaching physics?
Ready to ride?
I don't think so, Mom.
Not today.
Oh, sweetie.
Hemorrhoids acting up again?
You don't know the half of it.
Oh, yes, I do.
Try a dab of this.
"Rose-scented Preparation-H
for women?"
Now, the H is for her.
- I'm proud of you.
- Shh. Here comes my joke.
How you doing?
Sitting pretty.