Mmm...
Gentlemen, I put it to you.
The worst tapioca pudding is better than
the best pudding of any other flavor.
First off, that is axiomatically wrong,
because the best pudding is chocolate.
Secondly, the organic structure of tapioca makes it
a jiggling bowl of potential death.
It is extracted from the plant-
Hey, I'm thinking of growing a mustache.
No kidding! Foo Man Choo! A handlebar pencil.
Sheldon: It is extracted from the plant-
Howard: I'm not sure yet. You know, George Clooney has one now!
Really? I once saw him shopping at Ralph's.
He was buying tequila.
You think a guy like that would have some kind of booze lackey.
Alright this is cruel,
we better let him finish before his head explodes.
Alright Sheldon, why is tapioca...
Tapioca is extracted from the root of the plant Manihot esculenta.
Due to a high concentration of cyanide,
it is poisonous in its raw form
and lethal if prepared improperly.
Feel better now?
It is also indigenous to Brazil, as is the Cocoa Bean,
from which we get chocolate, the best pudding.
And you promised you wouldn't do that anymore!
Hey Hofstadter!
Hey Kripke.
Read about your latest proton decay experiment,
20 thousand data runs and
no statistically significant results.
Very impressive!
What a jerk.
Don't feel bad Leonard,
negative results are still results.
Even 20 thousand of 'em.
Alright.
Please don't cheer me up anymore.
C'mon, don't let him get to you.
It's Kripke.
Yeah, he's a... ginormous knob.
That's why he eats by himself,
instead of sitting here at the cool table.
Fo' shizzle.
Hey it's true, Kripke lacks the basic social skills that we take for granted.
But he also controls the new open science grid computer
that I need to use to run some simulations of
structure formation in the early universe.
Good luck getting time on it.
The only people he lets use it are his friends.
Well then, the solution is simple.
I shall befriend him.
Kripke!
Yeah?
What'd you say of the idea of,
you and I becoming friends?
I would say, I have no interest in becoming your friend.
Really? That seems rather short-sided,
coming from someone who is generally considered
altogther unlikable.
Why don't you take some time to reconsider?
Yeah, I'll do that.
Well I think we're off to a terrific start.
The Big Bang Theory S02E13
The Friendship Algorithm
Subtitled by blued888
www.eclecticelectronics.net
There you go.
Now any e-mail from Wolowitz
will go right into your spam folder.
Thanks!
I mean the e-mail doesn't bother me as much as
the vacation pictures of him in a bathing suit.
Yeah, I got the same one.
And that's not a bathing suit, it's a tan line.
Hello. This is Sheldon Cooper.
I'm leaving a message for Barry Kripke.
Barry, It was pleasant seeing you today in the cafeteria.
I saw that you purchased the chef's salad.
Apparently, you did not know that the chef's salad
is kitchen trickery, to utilize scrap meat.
Nevertheless, I hope you enjoyed it.
I'm following up on our pending friendship,
and I look forward to hearing from you regarding its status.
Sheldon Cooper.
What's up with Ichabod?
Oh he's trying to make a new friend.
Oh really? Well, good for him.
Well, unless he's makes one out of wood like Gepetto,
I don't think it's gonna happen.
Well, how did you guys become friends?
There was a fire on the bulletin board at the university.
Roommate wanted. Whistlers need not apply.
And you moved in anyway?
I assumed he was joking.
You'd be surprised how many
particle physicists have a whimsical side.
Oh what about Howard and Raj you mean?
How did you become friends with them?
I don't know...
How do carbon atoms form a benzene ring?
Proximity and valence electrons.
Well yeah, sure. When you put it that way.
But it all worked out, right?
I suppose.
I do miss whistling though.
Oh come on. Really?
(Whistles)
1st warning.
(Knocks) Penny.
This is for you.
Hello Sheldon.
Hi.
What is this?
It's a questionnaire I devised.
I'm having some difficulty bonding
with a colleague at work.
So I'm doing a little research to better understand
why my current friends like me.
Yes. Well, that is a good question.
But is this really the best way to figure it out?
Yeah, I agree.
The social sciences are largely hokum.
But, short of putting electrodes in your brain and monitoring
your response to my companionship, this is the best I can do.
Okay, question 1. Rank the following aspects of
Sheldon Cooper in order of appeal.
Intelligence.
Ruthless attention to hygiene.
Playfulness.
Java applet writing?
I know, I may have started off with a fairly obvious one.
You did an aspect of my most appealing trait, playfulness.
Why just go ahead and rank that number 1.
I'm afraid you're on your own for the rest.
It should take you no more than 3 hours.
Wait! How many questions are on this thing?
Only 211.
Don't worry, in deference to you,
I've kept them on a high school graduate reading level.
Thanks pal.
You got it...
Buddy.
Sheldon honey, did you ever consider making friends
by being, I don't know, pleasant?
Well that's certainly a thought-provoking hypothesis.
May I suggest it as the topic for your... essay.
(Tuts)
Your questionnaire, very disappointing.
I answered every question Sheldon.
You answered the multiple choice questions in a pattern.
A B B A C. A B B A C.
Aw, you picked up on that huh?
How could I not?
Come on! There's over 200 questions.
And look at some of these things.
Sheldon is to camaraderie, as the space shuttle is to blank?
There are a number of acceptable answers,
for example, C: near earth's transport, but certainly not B: avocado rancher.
And your essay, suggesting that I'd have better luck
making friends if I wait 'til the Cylons take over?
Please.
Hold on. I put some real work into that!
Yes, well it's better than what Wolowitz did.
He drew a raccoon with what appears to be, a distended scrotum.
It's kinda cute.
Until you get to the scrotum.
What hope do I have for establishing new relationships
given that my current friends apparently cannot take
a few hours out of their lives to help me?
Sheldon, I'm not going to defend a big bald raccoon.
I don't see how you could.
What I'm trying to say is that, maybe you can't approach this as a purely intellectual exercise.
What do you mean!?
Well, remember when you tried to learn how to swim using the internet?
I did learn how to swim.
On the floor.
The skills are transferrable.
I just have no interest in going in the water.
Then why learn how to swim?
The ice caps are melting Leonard. In the future, swimming isn't going to be optional.
But you do bring up an interesting point.
I don't have to break new ground here.
I'm sure much of the research already exists.
No... no, my point is, if you wanna learn how to make friends,
then just go out to a coffee shop,
or a museum. Meet people. Talk to them.
Take an interest in their lives.
That's insane on the face of it.
Come on.
Where are we going?
You're driving me to the mall.
I'm going to acquire a book that summarizes
the current theories in the field of friendmaking.
Why don't you just lie down on the floor and swim there?
Coping with the death of a loved one.
My condolences.
Thank you.
Family or friend?
Family.
Too bad.
If it'd been a friend, I'm available to fill the void.
It's just as well, she smelled like moth balls.
Okay, if you're gonna start sniffing people, I'm gonna go get a hot pretzel.
Excuse me.
Do you have any books about making friends?
Uhm, yeah but they're all for little kids.
I assume the skills can be extrapolated and transferred.
Uh, I guess.
They're right over there by the wooden train set.
Oh! I love trains!
I bet you do.
Oh my! That's awfully sticky.
Alright... Let's see.
Bernie Bunny has Two Daddies Now.
It's probably about homosexual rabbits.
Jerry the Gerbil and the Bullies on the Bus.
Read it, not helpful.
Oh! Here we go.
Stu the Cockatoo is New at the Zoo.
Author Sarah Carpenter lives in Fort Wayne, Indiana, with her
husband and bestfriend Mark.
And their cockatoos too.
Hardly makes her an expert in making friends, wouldn't you agree?
I don't like birds, they scare me.
Me too!
Most people don't see it.
What are you reading?
Curious George.
Oh I do like monkeys!
Curious George is a monkey.
Somewhat anthropomorphized but yes.
Say, maybe sometime you and I can go see
monkeys together. Would you like that?
Okay.
Sheldon, what are you doing?
I'm making friends with this little girl.
What's your name?
Rebecca.
Hi Rebecca, I'm your new friend, Sheldon.
No you're not, let's go.
We were really hitting it off.
Don't look up, there's cameras.
I'm curious. In the "How Well Do You Know Sheldon" section,
what do you put for his favorite amino acid?
(Leonard and Howard at the same time)
Lysine.
Damn it. I had Lysine and changed it.
Oh good! You're just in time.
I believe I've isolated the algorithm for making friends.
Sheldon, there is no algorithm for making friends!
Hear him out. If he's really on to something,
we can open a booth at Comic-Con, make a fortune.
See, my initial approach to Kripke,
had the same deficiencies
as those that plagued Stu the Cockatoo, when he was new at the zoo.
Stu the cockatoo?
Yes, he's new at the zoo.
It's a terrific book. I've distilled its essence into a
simple flowchart that would guide me through the process.
Have you thought about putting him in a crate
while you're out of the apartment?
Hello, Kripke. Sheldon Cooper here.
It occurred to me you hadn't returned any of my calls
because I hadn't offered any concrete
suggestions for pursuing our friendship.
Perhaps the two of us might share a meal together...
I see.
Well then perhaps you'd have time for a hot beverage.
Popular choices include tea, coffee, cocoa...
I see.
No, no, no, wait. Don't hang up yet.
What about a recreational activity?
I bet we share some common interests.
Tell me an interest of yours.
Really? On actual horses?
Tell me another interest of yours.
Oh no, I'm sorry, I have no desire to get
in the water until I absolutely have to.
Tell me another interest of yours.
Uh-oh, he's stuck in an infinite loop.
I can fix it.
Mmhmm. Mmhmm. It's interesting.
But isn't ventriloquism, by definition, a solo activity?
Yeah? Tell me another interest of yours.
Hmmm.
Is there any chance you like monkeys?
What is wrong with you?
Everybody likes monkeys.
Hang on, Kripke.
A loop counter? And an escape to
the least objectionable activity!
Howard, that's brilliant! I'm surprised you saw that.
Gee. Why can't Sheldon make friends?
Alright Kripke, that last interest strikes me
as the least objectionable
and I would like to propose that we do that together.
Tomorrow.
Yes, I'll pay.
Alright, goodbye.
Alright!
Time to learn rock climbing.
You know, I am a fan of ventriloquism.
Maybe you, me and your dummy
could go get a hot beverage.
He could talk while you drink.
No, I wanna climb some rocks.
This appears significantly more...
monolithic than it did on my laptop.
No one expects to see Hominids
learning to use bones as weapeons.
You afraid of heights, Cooper?
Hardly. Fear of heights is illogical.
Fear of falling, on the other hand,
is prudent and evolutionary.
What would you say is the minimum altitude
I need to achieve to cement our new-found friendship?
Come on, they have birthday parties here.
Little kids climb this.
Little kid Hominids, perhaps.
Is this your entire job?
Your parents must be so proud.
Let's go, Cooper.
Coming, Kripke.
Okay. Harness seems to be secure.
Small amount of incontinence just now,
but the website said that's to be expected.
Hey, this isn't so bad.
I feel like vertical swimming.
Hey, look at you, Cooper.
You're almost halfway to the top.
I am?
I was wrong.
It IS a fear of heights.
You alright there, Cooper?
Not really.
I feel somewhat like an inverse tangent function
that's approaching an asymptote.
Are you saying you're stuck?
What part of an inverse tangent function
approaching an asymptote did you not understand?
Understood all that. I'm not a moron.
Just keep going.
Yeah, I don't think I can.
Well, then. Climb back down.
No, that doesn't seem any more likely.
So what's the plan, Cooper?
Well, it's not exactly a plan
but I think I'm going to pass out.
I'm sorry. Can we please just do it one more time?
Okay.
1, 2, 1, 2, 3 and...
(Whistling altogether)
It's a little thing but you really do miss it.
Hello, everyone.
I brought my new friend, Barry Kripke, home for dinner.
Oh...
Hello to you, too.
How was rock climbing?
He passed out.
Just hung there like a big salami.
That's where I sit.
Ooh, you have a special spot.
What kind of wacko are you?
How much time you got?
Want some Chinese food?
Terrific. Got any dental floss?
In the bathroom.
Be right back.
I gotta floss the Indian food out of my teeth
if I'm gonna eat Chinese.
Sheldon, are you okay?
Oh yes, I pass out all the time.
But, it was worth it.
I've made substantial progress in bonding
with Kripke, which brings me to an awkward moment.
What's that?
Maintaining five friendships promises
to be a Herculean task. So...
I'm going to have to let one of you go.
Me, me. Let it be me.
Leonard, you are my roommate, my source of transportation
and you help me fold my sheets
when they come out of the dryer.
You are safe.
Can I whistle?
Don't be silly.
Howard, you do not have a PhD.
Your cologne is an assault on the senses
and you're not available for video games
during the Jewish high holidays.
Guilty as charged. I'm out.
No. You, too, are safe.
Oh come on. What do I have to do?
Okay. You know what? I see where this is going.
I'm not one of you guys. I'm not a scientist.
So just-
Penny, Penny, Penny. Everything you're saying is true,
but please allow me to continue.
Raj, you're out.
The good question.
While you do provide a certain cultural diversity
to an otherwise homogenous group,
your responses to the questionnaire were truly disturbing.
How could you, for a moment,
think that my favorite amino acid is Glutamine?
He had Lysine but changed it.
Yeah. Shoulda, woulda coulda, Raj.
I like to floss before I eat.
So my gum pockets are open for new food.
Eww.
Hello.
How did I walk past you?
I'm Barry.
Penny.
Yeah, it's not a very hot name.
I'm gonna call your Roxanne.
Suddenly I'm looking pretty good, huh?
So uh, Kripke, I was wondering if there's any chance
you could get me some time on the open science grid computer.
No.
No? But we're friends!
I'm sorry.
No, my friend?
I'm confused. I was given an understanding that
you allow your friends time on the machine?
No, that's wrong. There's an official schedule.
I have no control over it.
Oh. This entire endeavor seems
to have been an exercise in futility.
Raj, you're back in.
He likes monkeys.
You gotta give him credit for sticking with it.
I didn't think he had it in him.
He almost made it to the top this time.
The Big Bang Theory S02E13
The Friendship Algorithm
Subtitled by blued888
www.eclecticelectronics.net