- Who wants the last dumpling?
- Ooh, me.
Penny, a moment.
We just had Thai food.
In that culture, the last morsel
is called the krengjai piece.
And it is reserved for the most important
and valued member of the group.
Thank you all for this high honor.
I've seen pictures of your mother.
Keep eating.
All right, honey, if we're gonna
make the movie, we should go.
(RAJESH CLEARS THROAT)
This may be hard for you to hear...
...but when I say "honey,"
I mean my fiancée.
(INAUDIBLE)
Yeah, well, now it means her.
It's okay if he wants to come.
Fine. But next time, we get a sitter.
- I gotta to work. I'll walk down with you.
- Wait.
Uh, which is closer
to the new train store in Monrovia?
The movie theater
or The Cheesecake Factory?
Neither of them are close.
I guess it doesn't matter
which one of you drives me.
Let's play a fun guessing game
to see who gets to take me.
All right. This four-letter word
describes either a printer's type size...
...or a compulsion to eat dirt.
- Okay, I'm not driving him.
- Penny, don't give up, you can get this.
Aren't you going with Sheldon?
No, I have no interest in model trains,
stores that sell them...
...nor their heart-breaking clientele.
Oh, well, I have some work to do,
so...
I can't imagine that would disturb me.
Carry on.
Okay. Wouldn't you be
more comfortable at home?
Not really, no.
Alrighty then.
I guess I'll just get started.
Please, I don't need
the running commentary.
(SIGHS)
- Amy?
- Yo.
- You okay?
- Oh, sure.
- I thought you were reading.
- I was.
Now I'm thinking about what I read.
You all right, Leonard?
You seem very uncomfortable.
I... I'm fine.
Should I go?
I've been told sometimes
I overstay my welcome.
What...? Who told you that?
Well, most recently, my gynecologist.
Oh, you stay as long as you'd like.
I'm glad to hear you say that
because I'm having a wonderful time.
Hmm. I said the same thing
to my gynecologist.
What are you gonna get
at the train store, Sheldon?
Oh, I'm not buying anything.
They're having a lecture.
"HO gage railroading.
Half the size of O gage,
but twice the fun."
It's a very controversial topic.
- Which side do you come down on?
- I'll let you know after tonight.
Unlike some people,
I'm going in with an open mind.
Who am I kidding?
Of course we all know
it's O gage or no gage.
Can you believe grown men
sit around and play with toy trains? Heh.
That's big talk...
...for a man with a closet full
of magic tricks at his mother's house.
First of all, they're not tricks.
They're illusions.
Secondly, when we get married,
they're all going up in the attic...
...so you can have that closet
for clothes.
Why would I keep clothes
at your mother's house?
Well, don't think of it that way.
Once we move in, it'll be our house.
Is she moving out?
Why would she move out?
It's her house.
Hang on. You seriously think
I'm gonna live with your mother?
Howard, I think I can help here.
Yes, Bernadette,
that's exactly what he thinks.
Why not?
It's a great house, plenty of room.
If we have kids, Mom's there to help.
When she tells "The Three Little Pigs"...
...she actually has hair
on her chinny chin chin.
(CHUCKLES)
I'm not gonna live with your mother.
Not now, not ever.
Wow, someone obviously has
some mommy issues.
Raj, take me home.
Don't listen to her.
Go to the movie theater.
- Take me home now.
- Movie theater.
(GROANS)
Okay, everybody, calm down.
There is a simple solution here.
Raj, take me to the train store...
...and then I don't care
what you people do.
How was your shower?
Good, good.
Just out of curiosity,
what time do you usually go to bed?
Oh, I'm up all night.
I'm like a possum.
Boy, you were not liked in high school,
were you?
- Not really. Is that my yearbook?
- Mm-hm.
"Dear Leonard,
you're really good at science.
Maybe one day you'll come up
with a cure for being a dork."
It wasn't spray-painting
a lightning bolt on my briefcase.
- I can tell you that.
- If it makes you feel any better...
...the only person who signed
my yearbook was my mother.
Aw.
"Dear Amy, self-respect and a hymen are
better than friends and fun. Love, Mom."
(DOOR OPENS)
Well, you can add Jerry's Junction
to the list of train stores...
...Sheldon Cooper
will never set foot in again.
- Rough night, Casey Jones?
- You don't know the half of it.
It was billed as a lively give-and-take
on the merits of model-train sizes.
But it was actually a set-up...
...to intimidate weak-minded, spineless
rubes into buying HO starter sets.
- What's in the bag?
- I don't wanna talk about it.
But it's not a spine, I'll tell you that.
I had a delightful evening.
We should do this again sometime.
Uh, sure. That'd be nice.
Glad to hear it. I need someone
to accompany me to the wedding...
...of Dr. Moranelli and Dr. Gustufson
this Friday.
They're kind of the Brad and Angelina
of the Primatology Department.
- Wouldn't you rather bring Sheldon?
- I would...
...but the last wedding we went to
was a disaster.
- He behaved like a child the entire time.
- It's not my fault.
You said there'd be other scientists there
my age.
Doesn't matter. You're out. He's in.
No date to the prom,
two dates to a wedding.
Hmm, how times change.
Ha, ha, you have to go to a wedding.
(RINGS)
HOWARD:
I'll get it.
MRS. WOLOWITZ: Could you get it?
HOWARD: L said I'm getting it!
MRS. WOLOWITZ: Fine, I'll get it.
HOWARD: L got it!
Oh, hi.
Hey.
I don't wanna fight.
I was just surprised when you sprung
the living-with-your-mom stuff on me.
Yeah, well,
I'm sorry I didn't run it by you first.
MRS. WOLOWITZ: I don't know
who you're talking to, but in or out!
We don't need bugs!
The bugs only come here...
...because you're their queen!
Listen, how about this?
Before we make any decision
about where we live, we have a trial run.
You know, stay here for a weekend,
see what it's like.
- Your mom would be okay with that?
- Sure, she would.
Ma, do you mind if Bernadette
stays here this weekend?
MRS. WOLOWITZ: Hey, if she's
willing to give the milk away for free...
...who am I to say no?
See? She's good with it.
(CHUCKLES)
MRS. WOLOWITZ: Frankly, after all
your sleepovers with the little brown boy...
...a girl is a big relief.
All these years, I've been so wrong.
The tinier the train,
the more concentrated the fun.
You're a brain scientist.
Can you explain why a brilliant man
likes playing with toy trains?
Not without cutting his head open, no.
How about making my eyes
like Cleopatra?
Really? For a wedding?
You're right.
My cheek bones and beckoning pelvis...
...already have a certain
"Hello, sailor" quality.
I'm ready.
PENNY:
Aw.
So handsome.
Like James Bond.
Better than James Bond
because he's tinier.
I got you this to give to me.
Oh, sweetie, guests don't normally
wear corsages to a wedding.
That's more of a prom thing.
I never went to my prom.
My mom paid my cousin to take me
but he just used the money to buy drugs.
Put the corsage on her.
Amy, this is for you, heh.
When you're done copping a feel,
that goes on my wrist.
All aboard. Woo-woo!
It's official. I'm an HO trainiac.
So dinner went nice.
Yeah. Yeah, I guess.
Does your mother always cut your meat
for you?
Only when it's fatty.
Well, don't be jealous, babe.
Someday, you'll get to cut it for me.
MRS. WOLOWITZ: Bernadette,
I found the extra head for the Water Pik...
...if you wanna use it.
I'm okay, Mrs. Wolowitz.
MRS. WOLOWITZ: You sure? I just squirted
half a brisket out of my teeth.
Hey, Ma, how about a little privacy?
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
Oh, I know what that means. Hubba-hubba.
- Oh, God.
- Relax, it'll be fine.
BERNADETTE: Okay.
HOWARD: Heh.
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
Let me know when you're done canoodling.
Mommy needs a foot rub.
Do a little dance
Make a little love
Get down tonight
Do a little dance
Make a little love
Get down tonight
Would you like to dance?
No, thank you.
I'm really not much of a dancer.
You're not exactly winning any trophies
as a conversationalist, either.
I'm sorry.
The bride and groom seem happy.
Why shouldn't they be?
They have a feverish night...
...of socially-approved copulation
ahead of them.
In some cultures,
we'd stand outside their room...
...cheering as they achieved orgasm.
That sounds like a late night,
and I have work in the morning, so...
Leonard, you may not have noticed,
but I am being a delight here.
You're not holding up your end
of the evening.
I'm sorry.
This wedding just reminds me...
...of my kind-of-sort-of girlfriend
9000 miles away.
I have a kind-of-sort-of boyfriend
playing with a model train right now.
You don't hear me bitching about it.
A word of advice.
Moody self-obsession is only attractive...
...in men who can play guitar
and are considerably taller than you.
I'm not moody, I'm fun.
Do you have any evidence
to support that statement?
Well, hey,
I'm just as much fun as you are.
Really?
Are you willing to draw a mustache...
...on your finger
as a conversational icebreaker?
I am.
Okay, fine. What do you suggest?
We just had a lovely meal.
The band is on fire.
And you're sitting next to a beautiful
woman wearing whorish makeup.
Why don't we head out on the floor...
...and see if I can sweat
through these dress shields?
Once again,
I'm really not much of a dancer.
Don't worry, I'll lead.
(BAND PLAYING "CHICKEN DANCE")
(MIMICKING LIGHTSABER BUZZING)
Howard?
(MIMICS LIGHTSABER
POWERING DOWN)
- Ready for bed?
- No. I need to brush my teeth...
...but your mother's been
in the bathroom for an hour.
Oh, yeah, she sometimes
has problems doing her business.
Hang on, ahem.
Ma, give up!
Tonight's not your night!
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
You don't know that, I just sat down!
HOWARD:
Come on, take a break.
Bernadette needs to brush her teeth.
MRS. WOLOWITZ: She can come in
and brush her teeth. I'm not embarrassed.
Problem solved.
(CHUCKLES)
No, it's not. I'm not going in there.
Oh, come on, honey. She's just
sitting in there reading a magazine.
You can't see anything.
I go in all the time.
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
Ha! The eagle has landed.
(TOILET FLUSHES)
And we have splash down.
(HOWARD CLEARS THROAT)
Wait here.
I'm gonna go light a candle.
And then we make passionate love.
(LEONARD GRUNTING)
- There we go, last floor.
- I just can't figure out what happened.
I put my left leg in,
I took my left leg out.
and something just snapped.
The Hokey-Pokey
is a young man's game.
(CHUCKLES)
I did have a great time.
Thank you for reminding me
it's okay to have fun once in a while.
You're welcome.
Also for breaking the head
off the ice swan...
...so I could hold it
against my pulled groin.
I excel at spatial reasoning,
and I had a hunch...
...that the graceful slope of its neck
would cradle your genitals nicely.
Well, okay. Again, thank you.
And again, you're welcome.
- Wanna come in, have a cup of tea?
- No, I'm gonna head home.
Okay, well, good night.
Good night.
Ames, hi. How was the wedding?
Great. Until I accidentally made
Leonard fall in love with me.
Come in, let's talk.
Do you want a glass of wine?
Wine is one of the reasons
I'm in this fix.
That and this dang pelvis.
Okay, I'm sorry,
what exactly happened?
The inevitable. He was lonely and
vulnerable from missing his girlfriend.
While I was charming, supportive,
and let's face it...
...in this dress, the perfect combination
of Madonna and whore.
- Oh, God, did he make a move on you?
- No, but it's only a matter of time.
How could I have not seen this coming?
Now I'm gonna have to break
the little sad sack's heart.
I'm sure he'll be okay.
Oh, Penny.
Much as I would treasure knowing...
...the two of us had been defiled
by the same man...
...Leonard just doesn't get
my motor running.
So, um, what are you gonna do?
Do you want me to talk to Leonard?
- Let him down easy.
- No. I'll let him have tonight.
I'll send him an e-mail...
...letting him know this body
is never gonna be his wonderland.
I mean, frankly, you've got a better shot
than he does.
Leonard, check it out.
I bought an N gage locomotive.
Half the size of HO.
Look, it fits in my mouth.
Sounds like you had a great night.
I did.
- How was yours?
- Not bad.
I had a lot more fun with Amy
than I thought I would.
- What do you mean by that?
- It turns out she really knows...
...how to help a guy loosen up
and have a good time.
Although, truth be told,
my groin's a little worse for wear.
Ow!
- Why'd you do that?
- To send a message.
She is not for you.
- What?
- Not for you.
Good morning, handsome.
Morning, Mom.
It's me.
Yes, it is.
And you're so pretty in the morning.
Your mom and I made you breakfast.
Oh, wow, heh,
so you guys are getting along?
Yeah, I guess.
We're very different people, Howard,
so communication's a little tricky.
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
Does he like the pancakes?
He didn't try them yet!
- Is there any butter? Heh.
- It's butter-flavored syrup.
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
So? What's the word?
He wants butter!
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
It's butter-flavored syrup!
I just told him that!
I don't need any butter.
If you want butter, I'll get you butter.
Well, I guess I'll cut these by myself.