you are considering
going into experimental physics,
my door is always open.
Once again, I'm sorry
that the demonstration
didn't quite work out,
but now we know what happens
when you accidentally spill
Peach Snapple into
a helium neon laser.
Short answer is... don't.
And now to tell you about the
theoretical physics department
is Dr. Sheldon Cooper.
Dr. Cooper?
SHELDON:
Forget it.
Excuse me.
Sheldon, we both
agreed to do this.
It's a waste
of time.
I might as well explain
the laws of thermodynamics
to a bunch
of labradoodles.
If you don't do this,
I won't take you
to the comic book store.
Hello.
Nice work with
the laser, by the way.
Looking out at your
fresh young faces,
I remember when I too was
deciding my academic future
as a lowly graduate student.
Of course, I was 14.
And I'd already achieved more
than most of you
could ever hope to,
despite my 9:00 bedtime.
Now, there may be one or two
of you in this room
who has what it takes to succeed
in theoretical physics.
Although, it's more likely
that you'll spend
your scientific careers teaching
fifth graders
how to make papier mache
volcanoes with baking soda lava.
Oh, good God.
In short--
any one who told you that you
would someday be able
to make any significant
contribution to physics,
played a cruel trick on you,
a cruel trick indeed.
Any questions?
Of course not.
I weep for the future
of science.
Now if you'll excuse me, the
latest issue of Batman is out.
Come, Leonard.
Laser demonstration's looking
pretty good now, huh?
The Big Bang Theory S02E06 - The Cooper-Nowitzki Theorem
Sync By GeR - http://gerdiffuse.free.fr
Transcript : YYETS
I love this time
of the year.
The leaves are turning,
there's a bracing chill
in the air.
Plus there's a whole new crop
of female grad students
about to put on just enough
winter weight
to make them needy
and vulnerable.
That's right, honey,
have another calzone.
Daddy can wait.
Isn't there a university policy
against dating
graduate students?
No, if you can talk to them,
you can ask them out.
Damn, there's always a catch.
Hey, guys.
Hey, Leslie.
So, dumbass, I heard you made
a grad student
throw up last night.
The truth can indeed be
a finger down the throat
of those unprepared to hear it.
But why should I cater
to second-rate minds?
Because first-rate minds
call you "dumbass"?
Oh, yeah? Well...
you're a mean person.
Excuse me, Dr. Cooper,
I'm Ramona Nowitzki.
I was at your talk
last night.
I think you're just brilliant.
That is the prevailing
opinion.
Oh, now I'm gonna throw up.
Howard Wolowitz,
department of engineering,
co-designer of the
International Space Station's
Liquid Waste Disposal System.
Ew.
Dr. Cooper, I've read
everything you've published.
I especially liked your paper
on grand unification
using string-network condensates
and wawondering
how you determined
that three-dimensional
string-nets provided
a unified picture of ferrnions
and gauge bosons?
Amazing, an intelligent
labradoodle.
Woof.
The fact is I'm quite
close to a breakthrough
in showing how neutrinos emerge
from a string-net condensate.
Oh, my God, that would
change the way we view
the entire physical universe.
It's what I do.
You know, the Pishkin-Wolowitz
Liquid Waste Disposal System
is turning a few
heads as well.
Again, ew.
You know, I'd love to hear more
about how you intend
to add neutrinos.
Could we get a cup
of coffee sometime?
I don't drink coffee.
I do. I love me a cup of joe.
Well, it doesn't have
to be coffee.
How about dinner?
I do eat dinner.
Great. I know a terrific
little Italian place.
I never eat
in strange restaurants.
One runs the risk
of non-standard cutlery.
Excuse me?
Sheldon lives in fear
of the three-tined fork.
Three tines is not a fork.
Three tines is a trident.
Forks are for eating,
tridents are for
ruling the seven seas.
What if I brought food
to your place?
That would be acceptable.
On Mondays, I eat Thai food.
Mee krob and chicken sate
with extra peanut sauce
from Siam Palace.
You got it.
I already have your address.
What a nice girl.
Sheldon, do you have
any idea what just happened?
Yes. Apparently I'm getting
a free dinner.
Oh, yeah, no, this thing's
majorly out of order.
See? Sorry.
That's okay.
Guess I'm taking
the stairs.
Where you going?
4-A.
Oh, are you here
to see Leonard?
No, Dr. Cooper.
Dr. Sheldon Cooper?
We're having dinner.
Sheldon Cooper?
Tall, thin,
looks a little like
a giant praying mantis?
He is cute, isn't he?
Sheldon Cooper?
Hi, Leonard.
Hey, Ramona. Come on in.
Thanks. Where should
I put this?
Uh, the kitchen's fine.
Hey, what are you doing?
I need to see this.
Uh-huh.
The viewing area's
right over there.
Sheldon, your girl... date...
person... Ramona's here.
Oh, hello.
Oh, sorry I'm late.
I just got so caught up reading
the draft of your latest paper.
Did you enjoy
the humorous footnote
where I illustrate
mirror-symmetry
by likening it to the Flash
playing tennis with himself?
So funny.
But the idea that you might be
able to incorporate gravity,
I have to tell you, I found
it  physically exhilarating.
My hypotheses tend
to have that effect.
I'm sorry I didn't
bring enough
for your friends.
I assumed we were
going to be alone.
Oh, yeah.
No, we were just going.
To watch, right?
No, come on, now,
we're going out.
Oh, come on,
we'll be quiet.
Let's go, let's go.
Okay, you two.
Have a nice...
whatever this is.
Okay, you guys, look,
I know this is none
of my business,
but I just... I have to ask--
what's Sheldon's deal?
What do you mean "deal"?
You know, like what's his deal?
Is it girls...? Guys...?
Sock puppets...?
Honestly, we've been operating
under the assumption
that he has no deal.
Come on, everybody has a deal.
Not Sheldon.
Over the years, we've
formulated many theories
about how he might reproduce.
I'm an advocate
of mitosis.
I'm sorry?
I believe one day Sheldon
will eat an enormous amount
of Thai food and split
into two Sheldons.
On the other hand,
I think Sheldon
might be the larval form
of his species,
and someday he'll spin a cocoon
and emerge two months later
with moth wings
and an exoskeleton.
Okay, well, thanks
for the nightmares.
Hey, do you want to
hang out with us?
What are you guys gonna do?
Uh...
My mom's making
a brisket tonight.
The one with the
little onions? Mm...
Yeah, I'm busy, so...
Good night.
Her loss. Let's go.
Brisket party!
B-to-the-R-to-the-I-S-K...
To-the-E-to-the-T...
* Ooh...
Don't.
Hey, aren't you
having breakfast?
Yes.
Are you experimenting with
nutritional suppositories again?
Not in these pants.
So... how'd it go with
Ramona last night?
Oh, great.
She's smart, insightful
and she has a very unique way
of, you know, revering me.
Here's your spinach mushroom
omelet .
Thank you.
Did anyone touch it?
Gloves were worn
by everyone involved.
I was vigilant.
Ramona pointed out that I've
been wasting 20 minutes a day
standing on cafeteria lines.
Time which would be
better spent
tackling the great physics
problems of our day.
You don't tackle
the big issues, Ramona.
You fence with them.
En garde. Riposte.
Touche.
Morning.
Hi, Leslie.
So, Sheldon,
I see you're
organizing your papers
for the Smithsonian Museum
of Dumbassery.
There won't be any room
until they get rid of the
permanent Leslie Winkle exhibit.
Oh, good one.
I see you got a grad student
to fight your battles for you.
I'll let you keep
your lunch money today.
Okay, Dr. Cooper is on the verge
of a breakthrough.
If you're going to stay,
you'll have to be respectful
and quiet.
Wait for me.
So have you worked
out the neutrino issue?
Well, to paraphrase Mozart,
all the subatomic particles
are there.
I just have to put them
in the right order.
You're so witty.
Aren't I?
(knocking)
Hey, guys,
this package came for...
Dr. Cooper is working.
Yes, I'm close
to a breakthrough.
Ooh, it tickles!
Sorry.
Holy crap on a cracker.
Hey, Penny.
Hi. You probably don't want
to go in there.
Why?
What are they doing?
The only way I could explain it
would be in a therapist's office
with dolls.
Hoo-boy.
Dr. Cooper's working.
Yeah, I can see that.
Sheldon, Halo night,
Koothrappali's. You coming?
Oh, yes, it's Halo night.
Let me just dry my tootsies.
You're not going to Halo night.
Yes, I am.
It's Wednesday.
Wednesday's Halo night.
Didn't a great man once say,
"Science demands nothing less
"than the fervent and
unconditional dedication
of our entire lives"?
He did.
And who was that great man?
Me.
Sorry, Leonard.
Seriously? You're not coming?
You heard her.
How can I argue with me?
Okay, well, once again,
you guys have a good...
whatever this is.
Dr. Cooper, I have
to tell you
your friends are
holding you back.
I prefer to think of it
as "I'm pulling them forward."
Halo night?
A man with
your intellectual gifts
doesn't waste an evening
playing video games.
He does on Wednesdays.
Not if he wants a Nobel Prize.
He does want that.
Does a man with my
intellectual gifts
play paintball on weekends?
What do you think?
Drat.
Now shall we get back to work?
I suppose.
Battlestar Galactica
comes on tonight.
I guess I can wait for the DVD.
And then never ever watch it.
* You can be my Yoko Ono
* You can follow me
wherever I go *
* Be my, be my,
be my Yoko Ono, whoa-oa *
* Now that I'm far away
* It doesn't seem to me
to be such a pain *
* To have you hanging off
my ankle *
* Like some kind of ball
and chain *
* You can be my Yoko Ono
* You can follow me
wherever I go *
* You can be my Yoko Ono
* Whoa-oa-oa *
* You can follow me
wherever I go. *
(hushed):
Penny! Penny!
Penny!
Sheldon, honey,
I've told you,
it's a small apartment.
You only have to knock
one time.
Please, please, I don't have
a lot of time.
Look, Ramona finally dozed off,
and I need you to help me
get rid of her.
Get rid of her how?
I don't know,
but apparently I'm in
some kind of relationship,
and you seem to be an expert
at ending them.
Excuse me?
I see man after man leaving
this apartment never to return.
Okay, first of all,
it is not man after man.
Dr. Cooper?!
Hide me.
Hide you?
I formally request sanctuary.
Why aren't you working?
Um...
she distracted me.
I told you, Penny,
I don't have time
for your nonsense.
I have important things to do.
Oh, man.
I know what's going on here.
Really?
Well, then will you
explain it to me?
You're in love
with Dr. Cooper.
Uh, yeah, no, that's not it.
Don't try to deny it.
He's a remarkable man,
but you have
to let him go.
Oh, gee, okay.
I know it's hard, but he's
a gift to the whole world,
and we can't be selfish.
Yeah, he's a gift all right.
Sisters?
Uh, sure.
Sisters.
Holy crap on a cracker.
(rhythmic tapping on wall)
Sheldon?
(tapping stops)
(tapping resumes)
What are you doing?!
It's Morse code.
Why?
So we can communicate
through the wall.
We are communicating
Yes, but the communication
is not encrypted.
I don't know Morse code.
It's very simple.
This is A (taps)...
This is B (taps)...
This is C...
Sheldon, I'm not going
to learn Morse code
at 3:00 in the morning!
All right.
Don't come in here, don't come
in here, don't come in here,
don't... Oh!
(sighs)
What's going on?
Shh!
Ramona's sleeping on the couch.
I know.
When is she going home?
Never.
That's the problem.
I need your help.
What are you talking about?
I'm invoking the Skynet clause
of our friendship agreement.
That only applies if you need me
to help you destroy
an artificial intelligence
you've created that's taking
over the Earth.
Come on! Don't nitpick!
Good night.
Shh. All right.
I'm invoking our
Body Snatchers clause.
The Body Snatchers clause
requires me
to help you destroy
someone we know
who's been replaced
with an alien pod.
Yes. She's in the
living room. Go.
I'll wait here.
Sheldon, what are you doing
out of bed?
Now! Do it!
You know you need your sleep
in order for your
cognitive processing
to perform at
optimum levels.
Now come on.
Godzilla clause?
Not unless she
destroys Tokyo.
Rats.
I've got it!
I finally reconciled
the black hole
information paradox
with my theory
of string-network
condensates!
RAMONA:
It's unbelievable!
It's paradigm-altering.
And I could not have done it
without you.
Oh, please, I just offered
a little encouragement.
It was a lot more than that.
You helped me work out the
masses of all the fermions
and you pumiced my hammer toe.
How can I ever repay you?
Well, would you consider naming
it the Cooper-Nowitzki Theorem?
Who's Nowitzki?
I'm Nowitzki.
Oh, you want me to share credit?
Uh-huh.
Get out!
Oh, hey, hi.
Oh, bite me!
Sisters?
Excuse me, Dr. Cooper.
I'm Kathy O'Brien.
I just finished reading
your paper
reconciling the black hole
information paradox
with your theory of string-
network condensates,
and it just took
my breath away.
Maybe when I publish it,
I'll include an inhaler.
Would you possibly have any time
for me to pick your brain?
Let's see. Today's Thursday.
Thursday nights, I eat pizza
from Giacomo's.
Sausage, mushrooms,
light olives.
Great.
I'll bring it to your place.
I have the address.
What a nice girl.
Sheldon, do you see
what just happened here?
Yes, I'm getting a free pizza.
More pad Thai, please.
Sheldon, you've already had
four servings.
You might want to slow down
a bit, buddy.
Just one more bite.
Sheldon?
Sheldon, are you okay?
I'm just so... full.
(gasps)
That's it. No more Thai food.
www.tvsubtitles.net