Oh, boy.
What?
I can't comment without violating
our agreement
that I don't criticize your work.
Then what was "Oh, boy"?
Great restraint on my part.
There's nothing wrong
with the science here.
Perhaps you mean a different
thing than I do
when you say, "Science."
Okay, how's that?
You actually had it right
in the first place
Once again, you've fallen
for one of my classic pranks.
Bazinga!
Now here's a
peculiar e-mail.
The president of the
university wants
me to meet him
at his office tomorrow
morning at 8:00 a.m.
Why?
It doesn't say.
It must be an emergency.
Everyone at the university knows
I eat breakfast at 8:00
and move my bowels at 8:20.
Yes, how did we live
before Twitter?
I guess you'll find out
what it is in the morning.
That's 14 hours away.
For the next 840 minutes,
I'm effectively one
of Heisenberg's particles;
I know where I am or I know
how fast I'm going,
but I can't know both.
Yet how am I supposed
to carry on
with this huge annoying thing
hovering over my head?
Yeah, I know the feeling.
* Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state *
* Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! *
* The Earth began to cool
* The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools *
* We built the Wall
* We built the pyramids *
* Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery *
* That all started
with a big bang *
Leonard? Leonard?
Leonard?
(sighs)
Sheldon, it's 2:00
in the morning.
Why is everybody keep telling me
what time it is?
Everybody?
You, the president
of the university, his wife,
their sullen teenage daughter.
That entire family is fascinated
by what time it is
and whether people know it.
You went to President Seibert's
house
in the middle of the night?
He didn't respond
to my e-mail,
his phone number
is unlisted.
Tell me what my
other option was.
You could have waited
until morning.
I know, look who I'm talking to.
Do you remember the grant
proposal I submitted
to the National
Science Foundation
to detect slow-moving monopoles
at the magnetic North Pole?
(tinkling)
Hardly a day goes by
when I don't think about it.
Aw, how nice.
Well, a space opened up
at the last minute on the NSF
expedition to the Arctic Circle.
Wait a minute.
(toilet flushes)
He offered to send you
to the North Pole?
Yes.
In fact, he was quite
enthusiastic.
He said, "Frankly,
if I could send you tonight,
I would."
Okay, well, do you
want to go?
Of course not.
I'm a theoretical physicist.
A career I chose in no small
part because it's indoors,
but if I'm able to detect
slow-moving magnetic
monopoles there,
I will be the scientis
to confirm string theory.
People will write
books about me.
Third-graders will create
macaroni-art dioramas
depicting scenes
from my life.
Sure, maybe a tableau of me
trying to pummel you to death.
Sarcasm?
Maybe.
I'm on the horns of a dilemma.
Can you imagine me, Sheldon
Cooper, at the North Pole?
Easy peasy, I'm doing it
right now.
I'm not good
with cold, Leonard.
How often have we had
to leave a movie theater
because I got a headache
from drinking
the Icee too fast?
I can't go.
Well, then don't go.
How can you say that?
The scientific opportunity
of a lifetime
presents itself and my best
friend says "Don't go."
All right, then go.
Listen to you.
How can I possibly go?
Sheldon, what are the words
I can say right now
to end this conversation
and let me go back to sleep?
Odd, President Seibert posed
the exact same question.
How was it resolved?
It wasn't.
His wife set their dogs on me
and rendered the question moot.
Just imagine.
If he says yes,
we'll have an entire
summer without Sheldon.
We could play outside.
We could sit on the left side
of the couch.
I could use the bathroom
at 8:20.
Our dreams are very small,
aren't they?
Good news, gentlemen,
I have tentatively accepted...
ALL:
Yeah!
Whoo-hoo!
...the invitation to join
the Arctic Expedition.
It's not gonna be
the same without you.
Godspeed.
Thank you,
but your sentiments
may be premature.
Ooh, I don't like
where this is going.
I would like to propose...
that the three of
you accompany me.
To the North Pole?
Yes.
Is this just so
we won't touch your stuff
while you're away?
I'll admit that
was a concern.
But the fact is,
I'll need a support team.
And the three of you
are my first choice.
Really?
Well, there are others
who might be more qualified,
but the thought of interviewing
them gave me a stomachache.
Now, I know I'm proposing
an enormous undertaking,
so why don't you take a few
moments to discuss it?
We're not really gonna go
to the North Pole
with him, are we?
SHELDON:
I'm still within earshot!
You may want to wait
for my door to close.
(door closes)
We're not really gonna go
to the North Pole
with him, are we?
Hang on. Let's talk about it.
This is a National Science
Foundation expedition.
I don't know how
we can turn it down.
Easy. Instead of saying,
"No, we don't want to go
on an NSF expedition,"
say, "No, we don't
want to spend
"three months stuck in a
cabin in the Arctic Circle
with an anal nutbag."
But if we were part of the team
that confirmed string theory,
we could drink for free in
any bar in any college town
with a university that has
a strong science program.
Howard, this is big science.
You could be the engineer
who builds the equipment
that puts us on the cover
of magazines.
I could also be the engineer
who builds the crossbow
that kills Sheldon.
You still might
get on a magazine.
So you guys are seriously
considering this?
Yes.
And you think you can
put up with Sheldon?
Well, I'm a Hindu.
My religion teaches that
if we suffer in this life
we are rewarded in the next.
Three months at the
North Pole with Sheldon,
and I'm reborn as a well-hung
billionaire with wings!
Well, gentlemen, have you
reached a decision?
I'm in.
Me, too.
Oh, damn it.
Peer pressure. Fine.
Excellent.
Just an FYI,
as I am the expedition's
team leader,
protocol dictates that
be phrased, "Fine, sir."
But don't worry,
there will be a briefing.
(imitates gunshot)
Penny.
(knocking)
Sheldon.
Penny.
(knocking)
Sheldon.
Penny.
(knocking)
Sheldon.
Penny.
(knocking)
Sheldon.
Penny!
(knocking)
Sheldon!
Penny!
What do you want?
I need access to the Cheesecake
Factory's walk-in freezer.
Now, honey, I already told you,
the hamburger meat is fresh and
stored at a safe temperature.
No. This is to train for a
three-month expedition to
the magnetic North Pole.
What?
I don't know how that sentence
could possibly confuse you...
but to elaborate, I'm
going to the Arctic Circle
with Leonard, Wolowitz
and Koothrappali.
You're all going?
Yes.
For three months?
Excuse me.
Is that a yes or
a no on the freezer?
The woman has the
attention span of a gnat.
PENNY:
Hey, Leonard.
Hey.
Sheldon says you're going
to the North Pole.
Yeah. Pretty cool, huh?
Yeah. I'm just a little
surprised you didn't tell me.
Oh, well, it all happened
kind of fast.
And we had to get physicals
and buy thermal underwear
and study up on, you know,
snow and stuff.
Sorry, I was gonna tell you.
Oh, hey, no, you don't
have to apologize.
There's no reason
you have to tell me.
I was just...
you know, surprised.
Yes, yes, you were busy,
you were surprised,
all very fascinating.
Now where do we stand
on the freezer?
Is he serious?
Actually, it would help.
All right, I'll see
what I can do.
So, three months
at the North Pole.
Wow, that is...
awesome.
Yeah.
I'm sorry, but at what
point do you put this
"see what you can do"
plan into action?
Just a warning, Sheldon--
The freezer locks
from the outside.
Did she seem upset to you?
No.
Oh, good, I got it right.
Are you upset?
A little bit.
Two for two.
I'm on fire.
I mean, I know she's not
my girlfriend or anything,
but wouldn't you think
she'd feel a little bad
that I'm going to be gone
for the whole summer?
That feels like
a bonus question.
I'm going to stop here
while I'm ahead,
but I had a great time.
is to acclimate us
to the use of tools
in extreme temperatures
such as we will face
in the Arctic Circle.
Where are your tools?
Right here.
All right, team, open
up your practice kits.
As the university
did not permit me
to bring the actual
equipment we'll be using
to the Cheesecake Factory,
because apparently,
I'm "ridiculous,"
I've provided substitutes
which will exercise
your fine motor skills.
Leonard, you will
be doing a series
of complex mathematical problems
on a vintage Casio model
1175 calculator
watch I received
when I won the Earth Science
medal in 3rd grade.
Treat it with respect.
Raj, you will be painting
sideburns and a Van Dyke
on a six-inch figurine
of Legolas the elf.
Now, remember,
a Van Dyke is a goatee
without a mustache.
Wolowitz, you will be completing
a series of delicate
surgical procedures
on the classic children's
game "Operation."
To begin with, you will
"remove funny bone for
two hundred dollars."
For this I went to MIT.
And begin.
(groaning)
I think I swallowed some paint!
I can't press any of the
buttons with my gloves.
Oh, son of a bitch!
Adversity is to be expected.
Continue.
(game buzzing)
Oh, boy, am I gonna get sued.
Okay, I can't do this.
Me either.
Gentlemen, use your imagination.
Innovate.
Did Han Solo let Luke Skywalker
freeze to death on the
ice planet of Hoth?
No.
He cut open a tauntaun
and used its internal
body heat to warm him up.
You heard the man.
Hold him down
and I'll cut him open.
Hang on, I know I don't possess
the tools of leadership,
but I don't understand why we
can't assemble the equipment
inside the hut and
then take it outside.
I hadn't thought of that.
I guess we're done here.
Here, drink slash eat this.
What is it?
Hot chocolate
with a stick of butter.
Okay, why?
Because in the frigid
temperatures in the Arctic,
we need to consume at least
5,000 calories a day
just to maintain
our body weight.
Sheldon, you know
I can't eat butter.
I'm lactose intolerant.
Way ahead of you, that's an
"I Can't Believe
It's Not Butter" stick.
But all the other guys
are going to the North Pole.
I don't care what the
other guys are doing.
If the other guys jumped
in the Bay of Bengal
and tried to swim to Sri Lanka,
would you follow them?
If you were standing
behind me nagging, I might.
Don't talk back
to your mother.
This trip is much too
dangerous, Rajesh.
No, it's not.
Howard, tell them.
Doctor and Mrs. Koothrappali,
namaste.
I understand your concern,
but if it'll make
you feel any better,
my mother is fine with me going,
and this is a woman
who kept a safety rail
on my bed until I was 17.
So, she has no problem
with her son being
eaten by a walrus?
That's very unlikely,
Mrs. Koothrappali.
If Raj dies,
it'll be from frostbite,
gangrene, acute sunburn
or being ripped to shreds
by a 1,500 pound polar bear.
Ma, I'm putting you
on speakerphone
with Raj's parents.
Can you tell them
that you're okay
with me going to the Arctic?
Arctic?!
I thought you said Arkansas!
I didn't say that.
You never listen to me!
He doesn't tell me anything!
He lives a secret life
because he's ashamed!
Hey, Leonard, can I talk
to you for a sec?
Sure, but let's
go out here
(Wolowitz's mom ranting)
where there's a little
less yelling and guilt.
What's up?
Well, I got you a little
going away present.
Oh, a blanket.
Oh, no, no, no,
not just a blanket.
See, it has sleeves.
Yeah!
So, you can, you know,
be all snoodled up
while you do
your science stuff.
Oh, wow, cool.
Oh, I'm gonna miss you.
See you later.
Bye.
MRS. KOOTHRAPALI:
I told you no!
Why don't you believe me?
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
'Cause it doesn't
make sense to me!
How can it be that
in the entire country
of India,
there isn't one
Outback Steakhouse?!
(knocking on door)
Sheldon... Sheldon?
I want a cookie, Meemaw.
Sheldon, it's me.
But Meemaw just made cookies.
Listen, I don't know if
I can go on the expedition.
What?
I don't think I can
go to the North Pole.
Okay, Leonard,
I know you're concerned
about disappointing me
but I want you to take
comfort from the knowledge
that my expectations
of you are very low.
Yeah, that's very comforting.
Comforting is a part
of leadership.
It's not a part I care for,
but such is my burden.
Terrific, it's just that
I don't think Penny
wants me to go.
Assuming that's a valid reason
not to go, which it isn't,
how do you know this?
Did she say it?
Not exactly.
But she said she was gonna
miss me and she gave me this.
What is it?
It's a blanket with sleeves.
Oh, that's clever.
Let me see if I understand
this correctly.
Her missing you
is an emotional state
you find desirable?
Yes, obviously.
All right.
Well, given that missing you
is predicated on you leaving,
logic dictates you must leave.
Yes, okay, but I'm gonna
be gone for three months.
What if she doesn't miss me that
long and she meets someone else?
She does have a short
attention span.
So, I can't go.
Leonard, you may be right.
It appears that Penny
secretly wants you
in her life in a very
intimate and carnal fashion.
You really think so?
Of course not.
Even in my sleep-deprived
state, I've managed to
pull off another one
of my classic pranks.
Bazinga!
Oh, Leonard, what time is it?
It's 7:00 a.m.
I'm sorry it's early,
but we're leaving soon,
and I needed to talk to you.
Okay.
What did you mean when you
said you're going to miss me?
Um, I don't know.
You'll be gone and I'll notice.
Okay, well, um, what about this?
What does this mean?
Wine, credit card
and late night television
are a bad combination.
All right, fine.
What about that really long hug?
What did that mean?
That wasn't a long hug.
It was at least
five Mississippis.
A standard hug is
two Mississippis tops.
Leonard, I don't know
what to tell you.
It was just a hug.
Glad we cleared that up.
Yeah.
I guess I'll see you.
Okay, have a safe trip.
Thank you. Bye.
Okay, bye.
(sighs)
Means I wish you weren't going.
Damn it.
What?
We're out of ice.
All right, men,
we begin initial assembly
and deployment of
the testing equipment
starting tomorrow at 0700 hours,
but until then,
you are all off duty.
I suggest you keep
the shenanigans to a minimum
as medical help is
18 hours away by dogsled.
What are you working on?
Crossbow.
Hey, guys, can I
just say something?
How about we take a
moment to think about
where we are right now?
This is literally
the top of the world.
Only a handful of people
in all of human history
will ever see what
we are going to see.
He's right.
Yeah, wow.
It is remarkable.
So, who's up for a movie?
Good idea, what do you think?
Ice Station Zebra or
John Carpenter's The Thing?
I say double feature.
Dinner's ready!
What are we having?
Reconstituted Thai food.
Did you bring the
dehydrated low-sodium
soy sauce?
Check.
Freeze-dried
spicy mustard?
Check.
Flash-frozen brown
rice, not white?
Uh, oh, sorry.
Not to worry.
(laughing):
I hid it.
Bazinga!
You're in my spot.
There's no time
for a crossbow.
Find me an icicle.
SHELDON:
Three months.
This is gonna be great!
Sync by honeybunny @addic7ed.com
www.addic7ed.com
Thanks to YYeTs.net for transcripts
www.tvsubtitles.net