Hey. So you guys ready
to order?
Since we come in
every Tuesday night at 6:00
and order the same exact thing,
and it's now 6:08,
I believe your question
not only answers itself
but also stands alongside
such other nonsensical queries
as "Who let the dogs out?"
and, uh, "How are they hanging""
Okay.
So, the usual, with extra spit
on Sheldon's hamburger.
Penny, a moment?
Do you have plans
this weekend?
Oh, gee, Amy, I'm sorry,
I'm actually pretty busy
this weekend.
Probably serving food
that was ordered today.
That's too bad. I was hoping
you could be my plus-one
at the Institute
of Interdisciplinary Studies'
symposium on the impact
of current scientific research
on societal interactions.
The what?
It's an annual
science conference.
We've all been invited to speak.
Oh! Oh, okay, well, you know,
like I said, I have plans, so...
Shame. Since you're
my best friend,
I thought it would be
a good bonding opportunity.
I'm your best friend?
Don't you read my blog?
Oh, don't feel bad.
I never read Leonard's, and
I used to sleep with him.
Do you know anybody else
who would appreciate
an all-expense-paid spa weekend
at a four-star resort
in Big Sur?
No, I really-- I'm sorry,
free what? Sorry, what, what?
I think her weekend
just opened up.
Wait, wait, just to be clear,
when you guys say "spa,"
does that mean the same thing
as when regular people say it?
Pretty much.
Except we keep
our shirts on in the sauna.
You know, it is going
to be difficult,
but I'm going to cancel my plans
so I can do this for my bestie.
Please don't touch my breasts.
I... I wasn't going to.
All right. I just want
to establish boundaries.
Boy, this is great. I haven't
had a vacation in ages.
In order to take a vacation,
one first has to work.
You know, for a smart guy,
you really seem to have a
hard time grasping the concept
"don't piss off the people
who handle the things you eat."
That does seem to be
a valid principle.
I trust Penny will adhere to
the "Official California
Restaurant Workers'
Solemn Oath of Ethics
and Cleanliness."
I don't believe
there's any such thing.
You lied to me?
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool ♪
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall ♪
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
♪ The Big Bang Theory 4x13 ♪
The Love Car Displacement
Original Air Date on January 20, 2011
== Sync, corrected by elderman ==
== for www.addic7ed.com ==
Good morning.
If I could have everyone's
attention, please?
I know we're all eager
to get on the road to Big Sur,
so if we focus, I'm sure we can
get through this orientation
in under a half an hour.
Then it's just Q&A,
quiz, safety drills,
pose for commemorative
group photo and we're off.
Don't worry. Just sit
next to me during the quiz,
and you can copy my answers.
Raj?
What are you doing?
I don't think so.
You've had your allotted
six ounces.
The first bathroom break
isn't until the Denny's
located near Bakersfield,
which is approximately
two and half hours away.
Remember, people, we're only as
strong as our weakest bladder.
Nobody cares about
your Kegel exercises.
All right. We have
seven people, and two cars.
In the lead car,
driven by Leonard,
will be... myself,
Amy Farrah Fowler,
and Penny.
Yes!
He had you in the other car,
but I got you upgraded.
Yay!
She made the case
that if we break down
in the middle of nowhere,
your Nebraska backwoods skills
and brawny hands
will give us the best chance
to survive in the wild.
Brawny?
They're bigger
than mine.
Red Leader to Red Five,
come in.
Howard, you promised.
WOLOWITZ
Fine. Red Five to Red Leader.
What do you want now?
It's 11:15. I'm requesting your
quarter-hourly location update.
Still right behind you.
Copy that, Red Five.
Radio contact is sufficient.
No need to extend
your middle finger.
So, Amy, I've
been wondering,
are you and Sheldon going
to be sharing a room?
No, we discussed it.
We decided we didn't want
to jeopardize our relationship
by getting to know
each other too well.
Indeed. Nothing sours
a friendship more
than over-familiarity
with someone's toilet routine.
I can vouch for that.
Hey.
Not you, him.
Oh. Thanks.
Although yours
was an eye-opener.
Don't worry, Penny.
You're my plus-one.
You'll bunk with me.
And FYI, travel
makes me constipated,
so I'm the ideal
hotel roommate.
Terrif.
Are we there yet?
I hope we get there in time
to see the keynote address.
Really? You want to see
the keynote?
Yeah, it sounds fun.
"Super bacteria:
global apocalypse or
exciting research opportunity?"
Actually, I was thinking we
could go straight to the room
and... take a nap.
Really?
And miss the keynote?
We can watch it later on C-SPAN.
Besides, I was really
looking forward to you and me...
napping together in the hotel.
Honey, if you're
that tired,
why don't you just take
a nap here in the car?
No, see, it's not...
Hang on.
It's Leonard.
Hi, Leonard.
LEONARD
Yeah, hi. Listen, I just
got a text from Raj.
He wanted me to tell you
that when Howard says "nap,"
he means "sex."
Thank you, Raj.
Are you... an element
in the actinoid series?
No.
Amy?
Are you usually radioactive
when found in nature?
No.
Are you in the
lanthanoid series?
Amy, it's Penny's turn.
Penny?
Uh, I don't know...
Are you food?
That's not apropos.
We've already established
I'm found in the periodic table.
Well, it's a table, right?
I mean, why can't there
be food on it?
I knew she wasn't
lead car materiel.
Who elected you
Road Trip God?
Leonard.
It was a late-night vote.
We were all exhausted,
and he was threatening
to filibuster.
It's not technically
"Road Trip God""
it's Travel Supervisor.
Although Road Trip God
does have a certain ring to it.
I don't understand
why you people
just let him bully
you like this.
Someone should
stand up to him.
What's he going to do?
I can't believe you let him
kick me out of the car.
What could we do?
He's the Travel Supervisor.
Don't worry, Penny.
This is a better car anyway.
Yeah. It's the Love Car.
Should I ask?
♪ They say we're young
and we don't know ♪
♪ We won't find out
until we grow ♪
♪ Well, I don't know
if all that's true ♪
♪ 'Cause you got me,
and, baby, I got you ♪
♪ Babe ♪
♪ Mm da-da,
da-da, da-da ♪
♪ I got you, babe ♪
Red Leader, I'm really sorry.
♪ I got you, babe. ♪
WOLOWITZ AND BERNADETTE:
♪ I got you, babe... ♪
I missed you.
You know what?
I missed you, too.
Bernadette?
Oh, my God, Glenn!
Great to see you!
Are you here
for the conference?
Yeah, I'm doing
a global warming panel.
Oh, good for you.
Uh, Glenn,
this is my boyfriend Howard.
Nice to meet you.
Hi.
Ow. Hi.
You're a lucky man.
Bernie's
a great gal.
Yes. "Bernie" sure is.
Well, I got to run.
The panel's tomorrow morning.
It's called, "Remembering Snow:
A Look Back."
I'll try to catch it.
Oh, great.
Bye.
Hey... Bernie?
Yeah?
Please tell me he's
your gay cousin.
No.
He was one of my professors
in college.
Oh! That's a relief.
Then we went out
for a year.
Come on, let's check in,
so we can take that nap.
No, it's not necessarily
proportional...
Shut up!
That green bag
is Dr. Cooper's.
Here's an extra five.
Make him wait.
Oh.
Right to the nap, huh? Okay?
Uh, so, this Glenn guy.
You say you went out with
him for, like, a year.
Do we really need to talk
about my old boyfriend now?
No. I guess not.
What is he, like,
six-four, six-five?
Six-seven.
Probably has a hard time
finding a suit that fits.
Is something
bothering you?
No. It's just...
What?
I'm just thinking.
If you had sex with that guy,
I mean, there's nothing
I can do here
that will make
any kind of... impact.
Howard, it's not a contest.
I love you.
I want to be with you.
Yeah, great, love you, too,
but...
If it were a contest,
I wouldn't have a chance, right?
You can't think
that way.
Yep.
Loser.
Howard, stop it.
Sorry. I just
never figured that
a guy like me going out
with a girl like you
would ever have to compete
with a guy like that.
Wait a minute, "a girl like me"?
What's that mean?
I'm... I...
Are you saying you
don't think I'm hot enough
to go out with a guy like Glenn?
No! No, I'm saying
exactly the opposite.
I'm too hot to go out
with a guy like Glenn?
Yeah, let's go with that.
Still nothing.
Remind me to try again
in an hour.
Will do.
So...
girl talk?
Um, sure.
What do you got in mind?
Do you subscribe to the Freudian
theory of penis envy?
Um, I never really
thought about it.
Why?
Sometimes I think it might be
nice to have one.
Really?
Not for sex, for convenience.
You can't deny that,
by comparison,
our internal plumbing
is extremely high maintenance.
Again, I've never given
it much thought.
We have time now.
Think about it.
Oh, good.
Hey.
Can I stay here tonight?
Yeah. Why, what happened?
Howard's a complete
and total ass.
Oh, yeah, that.
Come on in.
Thanks. I'll sleep
on the floor.
Not necessary.
Penny and I are perfectly
comfortable sharing a bed.
We are?
Of course, we're best friends.
Oh, right, right, the blog.
Word of warning, though.
I'm prone to night terrors,
so when I wake up kicking
and screaming, don't panic.
Just pin me down and stroke
my hair, and I'll be fine.
Hey, can I stay here tonight?
Shh-shh-shh.
Sheldon's asleep.
What's going on?
Well, Howard's a complete
and total ass,
Bernadette's in my bed,
and no matter how much you
stroke Amy's hair, she bites.
What?
Never mind.
Can I stay here or not?
Uh, sure.
All right.
So, how do you want
to do this?
Well, I'm not getting
in bed with him.
Yeah, it is
a little like
getting into
Dracula's coffin.
We're just gonna have
to make the best of this.
Okay, when you say
"make the best of it..."
Sleep.
Right.
So we'll just call
the middle here
the Neutral Zone.
The what?
Star Trek.
You know, the
Neutral Zone
between the Federation
and the Romulan Empire.
Oh, okay.
Just like old times.
Of course,
sometimes the Federation
and the Romulans
would enter
the Neutral Zone
to negotiate a
temporary truce.
Sweetie, let me put this
in a way you'll understand:
from the waist down,
my shields are up.
Got it, got it.
We can do all
kinds of stuff
from the waist up,
you know?
Go to sleep.
Good night.
Please tell me
you're not having coitus.
We are not having coitus.
Can you guarantee
that it won't happen
at any time during the night?
Yes.
No.
ANNOUNCER
Next on Turner Classic Movies,
Bridget Jones's Diary.
Oh, my God, I'm crying already.
Raj? Raj?
Raj?
I need to sleep
here tonight.
Why?
Howard is a complete
and total ass,
Bernadette is in Penny's
bed, Amy bites,
and Penny may or may not
have coitus with Leonard.
Okay. Come on in.
Leonard, are you asleep?
No.
I really appreciate you letting
me stay here tonight.
Sure, no problem.
I know it's kinda weird.
True dat.
"True dat"?
I've gotten a lot more street
since we broke up.
Right.
Still mad at me about that?
No. No, I understand.
I got too intense,
you had to back off.
Thank you.
I've gotten a lot better
at that, you know.
I've dated four different women
since we broke up
and I didn't tell any of them
that I loved them
and wanted
to have their babies.
Good for you.
Okay, good night.
Good night.
You know, maybe it wouldn't be
the worst idea in the world
to violate the Neutral Zone
for just one night.
Oh!
Hey, Leonard,
Sheldon kicked me
out of the room,
gave me your key.
Penny's here.
No, we don't want to watch
Bridget Jones's Diary!
Good morning and welcome
to Science and Society.
I'm Dr. Sheldon Cooper, BS, MS,
MA, PhD, and ScD.
OMG, right?
Perhaps that joke was a little
too hippie-dippy for this crowd.
All right then, we'll begin
with opening remarks.
Miss Rostenkowski,
would you like to start us off
by discussing
your assessment
of science's responsibility
to society?
Sure.
I think all branches
of science
have to move cautiously
these days.
It's not just giant
nuclear weapons
that can destroy
the world.
As a microbiologist,
I can tell you
even the tiniest organisms
can still tear you a new one.
Interesting.
I think what you might need
to know about my colleague
is that though she claims
her field of interest  is tiny organisms,
she certainly has spent
her fair share of time
around what we can assume was
pretty massive weaponry.
I think Mr. Wolowitz
needs to keep in mind
that the past
is the past.
But he should know
that I am the kind of girl
who could get all
the giant missiles she wants.
Are we talking about women
wanting penises?
Because I'd like to weigh in.
Dr. Koothrappali, would you care
to join the conversation?
Certainly.
I'd like to raise two points.
Number one, I think they are
talking about penises.
And number two, these mimosas
are kicking my little brown ass.
I'd like to kick
your little brown ass.
What did I do?
Oh, I don't know.
Maybe when you walk
into a hotel room
and you see a guy getting back
together with his girlfriend,
you should consider doing
something other
than crawling into
the adjoining bed.
I did. You said no
Bridget Jones.
We weren't getting
back together!
It was a one-time thing!
Excuse me.
We're not taking comments
or questions
from the audience just yet.
Oh, shut up, Sheldon!
Hi, bestie.
All right,
why don't we see if we can bring
this back to topic.
Let me ask you
something, Bernie.
I guess not.
How would you feel if
you met my ex-girlfriend
and she was like
Angelina Jolie?
Oh, come on, Howard,
be realistic.
What, I'm not hot enough
for Angelina Jolie?
I'd like to weigh in here.
No.
All right,
why don't we open it up
to Q&A from the audience?
Yeah, I have a question.
Is there anybody who can get me
the hell out of here
and back to Los Angeles
tonight?
I'm driving back to L.A. tonight.
Penny, that's Glenn.
Glenn, that's Penny.
No!
SHELDON
Red Leader to Red Five.
Red Leader
to Red Five.
Anybody up for a little game?
I spy with my little eye...
a nonferrous metal.
Must be out of range.
Leonard, can I ask you
a question?
Sure.
Are you bothered by the fact
that your former girlfriend
left the symposium
with what is probably
the most beautiful man
I've ever seen in my life?
No. Why do you ask?
Because we're going
120 miles per hour.
All right, if no one's going
to guess...
I was spying the aluminum rims
on the police car
we passed a few miles back.
== Sync, corrected by elderman ==
== for www.addic7ed.com ==