Why hast thou forsaken me, O
deity whose existence I doubt?
Here. Breathe
into this bag.
What's going on?
They stole everything, Leonard!
Everything.
Are you the roommate?
Yeah, Leonard Hofstadter.
What happened?
Your friend here called 911
to report a robbery.
Oh, my God,
what did they get?
What didn't they get?
They got my enchanted weapons,
my vicious gladiator armor,
my wand of untainted power,
and all my gold!
You called the police
because someone hacked your
World of Warcraft account?
What choice did I have?
The mighty Sheldor,
level 85 blood elf,
hero of the Eastern kingdoms,
has been picked clean, like
a carcass in the desert sun.
Plus, the FBI hung up on me.
Into the bag.
They took my battle ostrich!
- Oh, no, not Glenn!
- Yes!
Glenn!
The only bird I ever loved.
Good luck, fellas.
Oh. Well, thank you, officer.
Wait a minute!
You're not going to do anything?
Mr. Cooper,
there's nothing...
Dr. Cooper.
Seriously?
Not the kind with
access to drugs.
Fine. Dr. Cooper.
I'm sorry for your loss,
but the Pasadena
Police Department
doesn't have
jurisdiction in...
Pandora.
That's from Avatar!
World of Warcraft
takes place in Azeroth.
Goodness gracious, how are you
allowed to carry a gun?
Can you at least refer me
to a rogue ex-cop?
What?
Wh-- you know, one who was
drummed off the force
because he refused
to play by the rules,
and now he hires himself out
to impose his own brand
of rough justice?
No.
Thank you, officer.
It's all gone. All gone.
I'm really
sorry, Sheldon.
What kind of world
do we live in,
where a man would take
another man's battle ostrich?
I don't know.
This act of aggression
must be met
with swift and cruel ferocity.
It is time to cry havoc,
and let slip the dogs of war.
I'm on it.
Hi, Mrs. Wolowitz.
Is, is Howard there?
Okay, thanks.
That particular dog of war
will have to call you back
after his bath.
See if Raj is done with Pilates.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool ♪
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall ♪
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
♪ The Big Bang Theory 4x19 ♪
The Zarnecki Incursion
Original Air Date on March 31, 2011
-- sync, corrected by elderman --
Three thousand hours.
Three thousand hours
clicking on that mouse,
collecting weapons and gold.
It's almost as if it was
a huge waste of time.
Whoever did this
knew what they were doing.
He got in and out
of your account in under
15 minutes, transferred
all your stuff,
and didn't leave
a digital fingerprint.
Oh!
There isn't enough
chamomile tea in the world
to quell the rage in my heart.
Hold on. I'm talking to an orc
under the bridge
in Thunder Bluff
who says if we pay him, he'll
help us track down your things.
Can we trust him?
I should say so;
he appears to be a member
of the Nigerian royal family.
Whoa! Somebody's auctioning off
a jeweled ostrich bridle!
No. Glenn's was leather.
He was a simple ostrich.
Is! Is, I haven't given up hope.
Hey.
Hey, Penny. We're kind of in
the middle of a crisis, here.
Oh, I know. Bernadette told me.
Sorry, Sheldon. I know
that game meant a lot to you.
What-- "that game"?
Excuse me, Penny, but
Doodle Jump is a game.
Angry Birds is a game.
World of Warcraft is a
massively multi-player
online role-playing...
all right,
technically it's a game.
Bad news, the Nigerian prince
may be a fraud.
Okay, well, anyways,
I brought you
a day-old cheesecake
to cheer you up!
Stale pastry
is hollow succor
to a man who is
bereft of ostrich.
Just say "thank you."
I thought I just did.
All right. See you later.
Oh! Hello.
Oh, hi! I was just
dropping off a cheesecake
to Sheldon. He was robbed
of a bunch of imaginary crap
that's useful in
a make-believe place.
I don't know what that means.
Yeah, well,
sadly, I do.
Did you know last weekend
Priya took Leonard
rollerblading
at the beach?
Can you believe that?
I feel like I'm supposed
to say "that bitch,"
but I don't have
enough information.
I am the one who
spent two years
trying to get him to even
go to the beach
in the first place.
And he was so phobic about
stepping on medical waste,
I had to carry him
to the water.
I took Howard to the beach once.
He almost burst into flames
like a vampire.
So what's the thanks
I get for turning Leonard
into quality boyfriend material?
I have to tiptoe around
his new girlfriend.
I think you're on.
Oh.
That bitch!
Want some coffee liqueur
on your ice cream?
Ah, here's the alcohol
and drug peer pressure
Mother warned me about.
I was starting to think
it was never going to happen.
Yes, please.
You guys should've seen Leonard
when I first met him.
There was no eye contact.
He was either looking
up at the ceiling,
or down at his shoes.
I'm drunk.
You know, for the
first couple of months,
whenever I would
take off my bra,
he would giggle and say,
"Oh, boy, my breast friends!"
Well, if it makes you
feel any better,
I'm never speaking
to Priya again.
No, don't do that.
No reason to be mean to her.
This may be the
alcohol talking...
but I believe there is.
Are you familiar
with the recent study
of Tanzanian chimpanzees
by Nishida and Hosaka
out of Kyoto University?
No, but I can name
all the Kardashians.
Primates, such as ourselves,
have a natural instinct
to ostracize ill-mannered
members of the troop.
Bernadette's urge to
shun, scowl or
fling her waste at Priya
is hard-wired into her DNA.
I don't have an urge
to fling my waste.
Believe me, it's there,
we all have it.
Hit me with some more booze,
and I'll show you.
All right, here we are--
this is the tavern
where all the black-market
weapon trades go down.
I don't think my character
should be in a place like this.
Everyone's undressing
her with their eyes.
Maybe if you stop
dropping your sword
and bending over to pick it up.
Okay, what exactly
are we looking for?
Redheaded troll,
goes by the name of Glumly.
According to the
message boards,
if you want to
move stolen goods
and it's after school
hours, he's your guy.
Leonard,
is this going
to take much longer?
I thought we were
going to spend
some time together.
Uh, we are.
In the meantime,
you're welcome to whip up
a quick character and join us.
Seriously?
Well, you have to put
in a credit card number,
but it's fun.
Maybe I should just go home.
Our troll just walked
in! I got him!
We got him.
We're almost done.
So, how do
you guys want
to play this?
Be ruthless.
You tell him
if he doesn't start talking,
we'll register a complaint
with his Internet
service provider.
Sheldon, what if he gets his
Internet from his cable company?
He could lose his HBO and all their
delightful original programming.
I don't care!
I'm losin' it, man!
Why don't we play this smart?
Try a little
"good goblin, bad goblin."
Oh, dear Lord.
Nah, I think we have
to be more subtle.
Okay, I see where
this is going.
Fine, I'll have
sex with him.
That's not where it was going.
Good, because
I would hate that.
Leonard, you're busy--
let's talk tomorrow.
Oh, wait.
- Hang on. Are you upset?
- No, no, I think
it's sexy to date a boy
trapped in a man's body.
Oh.
Good, good.
I'll tell you
what happens.
And people think I
don't get sarcasm.
Well, well, well.
Look who it is.
Okay, be nice.
Hello.
Hi. We're just
heading out for a drink.
Because I do that now.
Count your blessings
you're not a Tanzanian chimp.
What?
Don't listen to her--
she's had a lot
of ice cream.
Do you want to join us?
Oh, thank you,
but I have work to do.
Four women walk
down the stairs--
how many reach the lobby?
Did your sister say anything
when you got home last night?
Oh, no, don't put me
in the middle of this.
I'm not going to
be your go-between.
Come on, help me out.
Am I in trouble?
There's no
reason to worry.
That's a relief.
I'm sure
many women
in happy relationships
spend their nights
Skyping with their
ex-boyfriend Sanjay.
Good news, gentlemen--
I found our hacker.
- What?
- Really?
Yeah. No one can hide from me,
not Waldo, not Carmen San Diego,
not even topless
Natalie Portman.
I've never said
these words before,
but good job, Howard!
Thanks. Our culprit
is one Mr. Todd Zarnecki, 2711
Ocean View Road,
Carlsbad, California.
The name and the address
drip with evil.
What else do we know about him?
Why, quite a
bit, actually.
I'll bet he's some loser
who lives with his parents.
Yes, he does live
with his parents.
Here's a Google Earth
shot of their house.
Excellent!
It's in a cul-de-sac.
We can box him in.
Hold on, you're thinking
of going there?
Carlsbad is only
a couple of hours away.
Fine.
You walk up to the house,
knock on the door
and demand your stuff back.
What if he says no?
I don't know if you've been
following the news, Leonard,
but there have been
some terrific advancements
in the field of torture.
No one's getting tortured.
Fine, we'll abide by
the Geneva Convention.
But ask yourself this:
in the course
of our lives,
how much lunch money
has been taken from us?
How many kites?
How many Scooby-Doo
Trapper Keepers?
I totally had one of those.
Of course you did.
It was a fun and practical way
of organizing your school work.
But the bullies
took it from us.
Well, no more.
Tonight, we take back
our dignity,
our birthright and our pride.
What do you say?
Who's with me?
I have a hip-hop aerobics class
at 5:00; could we go after?
Sure.
Also, tonight's the Sabbath
and my mother and I
have a tradition of
lighting the candles and
watching Wheel of Fortune, so...
If we could leave
at 8:00, we'd still be able to
regain our birthright
at 10:00, 10:30 latest.
Fine.
Leonard?
Oh, geez, I-I don't know
if I can ditch Priya
two nights in a row.
Oh, come on, man.
Bros before...
...my sister.
Aw, screw it.
I'm in.
Me, too.
And me.
One moment.
I'm hell-bent on catching
a cyber criminal,
not the common cold.
I'm sorry, I thought
this delay was
so you could watch Wheel of
Fortune with your mother.
I am.
She's just bleaching
her mustache.
Check it out.
Hey, Ma!
"Before and After!"
Four words, 17 letters,
two N's, one V!
"Fanny pack of wolves!"
That's incredible.
Yeah, she's kind of
a Wheel savant.
Uh-oh, that's Priya.
Sitar music for her ringtone
is not cool, dude.
Hit the...
Hey, sweetie.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
I'm gonna be working late.
Yeah, I-I miss you, too.
Okay, sure, I'll call you
when I get home.
Okay, bye-bye.
Very nice.
You lie to my sister.
That's the nicest thing
he does to your sister.
Oh, guess who.
Cover for me.
Hello, Priya. What's up?
How would I know
if Leonard's at work or not?
Don't be suspicious.
Look, if you want your
relationship with Leonard
to continue,
you're going to have to believe
whatever wild-eyed,
cockamamie excuse
the white devil
has the nerve to offer you.
Okay? Yeah, bye-bye.
You owe me.
New puzzle, Ma!
"Same name"!
One N, two D's, three O's!
Whoopi and Rube Goldberg!
That's uncanny.
I know.
It's her superpower.
Well, that and jiggling
her arm fat.
I can't believe we're going
all the way to San Diego
to confront this guy.
Yeah, we're kind of
bad-asses, aren't we?
Totally.
Hey, how about
we stay the night
and hit Legoland
in the morning?
Sea World is better.
It has Shamu, who is
literally tons of fun.
But for the moment, let's stay
focused on Todd Zarnecki.
Yeah, we're coming for you,
Todd Zarnecki.
And for the record, Legoland
is more interactive.
I almost feel sorry
for the poor fool, sitting in
his split-level suburban ranch,
unaware that
a vengeful horde is barreling
down the San Diego Freeway
at 71 miles an hour.
Ease up there, lead foot.
You trying to get us killed?
I took the liberty
of burning us
a mix of heroic
questing music.
This says "Beyonce
Bootylicious Dance Mix."
It's a
re-writable CD.
Just put it in.
Beyonce? Really?
She's curvy and she owns it.
I like that.
Oh, yeah, I'm feeling it.
We are winged fury!
Which is still no excuse
for going over
the posted speed limit.
♪ ♪
Next time we go to
kick someone's ass,
we take the train.
I always prefer the train.
Sheldon, let's go.
Coming.
Why did you bring that?
No weapon strikes more fear
into a man's heart
than a Klingon bat'leth.
Okay, let's get
clear on something.
We're just going to tell
this guy to transfer all of
your stuff back into your
account and then be on our way.
No one's bat'lething anybody.
So my blade shall not
taste blood tonight?
No.
Well, now I just feel silly
holding it.
Come on.
Can I at least
kick down the door?
You're welcome to try, but
the other day, it took you
15 minutes to get
into a FedEx box.
Who is it?
Your doom!
Don't say "your doom."
Who opens the door
for their doom?
Good point.
Basket of puppies.
What?
Uh...
Sheldon?
Are you Todd Zarnecki?
Yeah. Who are you?
I am Sheldor of Azeroth.
I want my things back.
I don't think so.
Let me see that.
Careful.
That's a collectible.
I know.
I've always wanted one.
Well, he's even more cunning
than we thought.
You know, the joke's on him.
Without the certificate of
authenticity,
that bat'leth is worthless.
Yeah, he walked
right into our trap.
Legoland seems like
a hollow dream now.
Uh-oh.
What's the matter?
Something's wrong.
I'm not getting any gas.
Anybody know anything about
internal combustion engines?
Of course.
19th-century technology.
Very basic.
Does anybody know how to fix
an internal combustion engine?
No. No.
Not a clue.
Well, we'd better call somebody
to come pick us up.
It'd be swell
if they had a train.
Thank you, Penny.
No problem.
So, Leonard,
I think it's interesting
you didn't call your girlfriend
to come get you.
Uh, I kind of
told her I was working.
So you lied to her.
Also interesting.
Yeah, she doesn't really
understand
the whole Warcraft
adventure-role-playing thing.
Well, doesn't matter if she gets
it, as long as she's pretty.
This one's funny,
Leonard.
How come you couldn't
make it work with her?
So did you at least get
Sheldon's fake stuff back?
No. We failed
in our noble quest.
How come?
Todd Zarnecki was mean.
All right. Hang on.
What are you doing?
I'm gonna show you how we
finish a quest in Nebraska.
Oh. Beyonce.
This ain't no Beyonce.
Now what?
Give my friend his stuff back.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Well, then, good news.
Today's the day a girl's
finally going to touch you
in your little special place.
Now give him his stuff back.
Okay.
We did it!
I said, "we."
Oh, hold the door.
- Oh, hi.
- Hi.
Going to see Leonard?
Yes.
How have you been?
Fine. You?
Very well, thank you.
-- sync, corrected by elderman --
All right, well,
great seeing you.
Yeah. You, too.
Amy's right.
I do want
to fling my poop at her.