You know who's got to be
the bravest person
in the Marvel Universe?
Whoever has to give
She-Hulk a bikini wax.
You want to talk brave,
how about Captain America's
undocumented Mexican gardener?
He's not braver than
whoever uses the bathroom
after The Thing?
As usual, you're all wrong.
The bravest person
in the Marvel Universe
is the doctor who gives
Wolverine his prostate exam.
How about the guy who gets
a prostate exam from Wolverine?
Now you're just being silly.
Wolverine's never displayed
the slightest interest
in helping others
prevent prostate cancer.
Hello.
Yes, the elevator's
out of order;
you'll have to use the stairs.
Of course you can.
Pizza dates back
to the 16th century,
while the first elevator
was not installed until 1852.
That means that
for over 300 years,
people carried pizzas up stairs.
Be part of that proud tradition.
I'll go get Penny while that guy
spits on our food.
Do you think they gave Wolverine
an adamantium prostate?
That's a stupid question.
We're having
a conversation about
probing the heinies
of superheroes.
There are no stupid questions.
Yes?
Oh, um, is
Penny here?
You're Leonard, right?
Yeah.
Damn, it's good
to finally meet you, son.
Okay, I think a bit of
context here might help.
Oh, hey, Leonard.
I see you met my dad.
Oh, good.
Context.
Come on in, buddy.
Take a load off.
Oh, gee, Dad,
Leonard can't stay.
He just dropped by to say hello.
Thanks for stopping by, sweetie.
I'll see you later.
Bye.
That was odd.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool ♪
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall ♪
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
♪ The Big Bang Theory 4x09 ♪
The Boyfriend Complexity
Original Air Date on November 18, 2010
== Sync, corrected by elderman ==
== for www.addic7ed.com ==
Are you sure you have
enough comics?
You're going to be monitoring
the telescope for 12 hours,
and by my estimate,
you've only selected
seven hours of reading material.
That's even factoring in
your difficulty in parsing
American comic book idioms
like "Bamf!" and "Snikt!"
Is that racist?
It feels racist.
Don't be oversensitive.
He's calling you illiterate,
not your race.
Oh, okay. Good.
I don't need
more comics.
Howard's gonna stop by,
we're gonna play
Intergalactic Battleship
and Indian Monopoly.
I don't care for
novelty editions of Monopoly.
I prefer the classics:
regular and Klingon.
Actually, Indian Monopoly's
just like regular,
except the money's in rupees,
instead of hotels
you build call centers,
and when you pick a Chance card,
you might die of dysentery.
Just FYI,
that was racist.
You'll never guess
what just happened.
You went out in the hallway,
stumbled into
an interdimensional portal
which brought you 5,000 years
into the future,
where you took advantage
of the advanced technology
to build a time machine,
and now you're back
to bring us all with you
to the year 7010
where we are transported
to work at the Thinkatorium
by telepathically controlled
flying dolphins?
No.
Aw.
Penny kissed me.
Well, who would ever guess that?
What-what kind of a kiss?
A big kiss. On the mouth.
Is it possible that she was
going for your cheek
and you moved
and she accidentally got lip?
That happens with me and my mom
all the time.
She introduced me to her father,
kissed me and then
shut the door in my face.
Maybe she was trying
to send you a message.
You think?
Yeah.
"This man is not my father.
"I'm being held hostage.
"So I'm going to do
"something insane in the hopes
that you'll call 911."
Penny kissing me is not insane.
She used to kiss me
all the time.
Einstein defined insanity
as "doing the same thing
over and over again and
expecting different results."
By that standard,
Penny is cuckoo for Cocoa Puffs.
I'm just saying,
it felt like it may have
meant something.
Ah, this takes me back.
Leonard obsessing about Penny.
I mean, don't get me wrong,
I love your new stuff,
but once in a while
it's nice to hear the hits.
Ooh, ooh!
Do "Our babies will be smart
and beautiful."
That one always makes me laugh.
Why do I bother
talking to you people?
If it'll make you feel better,
we rarely listen.
Hey, can I talk to you
out here for a sec?
Yeah, sure.
I'm starting to think we're
never going to see that pizza.
So you're probably wondering
what that was all about.
What, uh, the kissing
and everything?
Nah, women do that to me
all the time.
Yeah, okay.
The thing is, I kind of
told my father
we got back together again.
What? Why?
Well, you're the first guy
he's ever really approved of,
you know?
You're a scientist
who went to college
and you don't have a neck tattoo
or outstanding warrants
or... or a baby.
What kind of guys
did you used to go out with?
Just guys.
Anyway, when I told him
we split up, he was heartbroken,
and he kept bugging me:
"How's Leonard?
"Why can't you get
back together with Leonard?
I bet Leonard never
tipped a cow over on himself."
So to get him off my back,
I told him
we worked things out.
Really?
How-how'd we manage that?
What?
I mean, did you apologize?
Did you have to woo me?
Get over yourself.
I whistled, you came running.
Yeah, no, I don't think so.
Okay, why are you
arguing about this?
I'm just saying,
if we fake got back together,
that's totally not
how it fake happened.
Oh...
Okay, whatever.
Will you please just play along
until my dad leaves?
Hold on, you actually want me
to deceive your father
with some sort of
sham play acting and kissing?
'Cause I'm good with that.
Penny, you out here?
Come on, honey,
not in front of my dad.
Relax, I've seen you do
a lot worse with a lot stupider.
See?
He doesn't mind.
So, Leonard,
I'm taking your gal out
for a steak dinner;
you want to join us?
Oh, Dad, that's nice,
but Leonard has to work.
Right, Leonard?
Uh, I do, I
have to work.
But I'm gonna blow that
off to spend the evening
with my sweetie and her
father, 'cause, you know,
just the kind of
boyfriend I am.
Oh.
Come here, you.
C-7.
Miss.
How could that be a miss?
C-6 was a hit, C-8 was a hit.
Part of your starship
has to be on C-7.
Not if it has a hole
in the middle.
What kind of spaceship
has a hole in the middle?
A Romulan Battle Bagel?
Knock-knock.
Oh, great, you made it.
Come on in.
I invited her.
So where's
the telescope?
It's in Hawaii, but Raj
controls it from here.
He's hoping to see Epsilon
Eridani dim, which would be
evidence of a planet
orbiting it.
So we just sit and stare
at the screen,
waiting for
something to happen?
I did it with you when
we rented The Notebook.
Yes, Gena Rowlands
is a treasure.
You'd better open up
that bottle of wine
or I'm gonna end up
with swimmer's ear.
Excuse me.
I can't be drinking,
I'm about to make
an important scientific
discovery here.
What? Galileo did his best work
while drinking wine.
How do you know that?
Well, he was Italian.
It's a reasonable assumption.
Dude, can you even
open your mouth
without spewing a
cultural stereotype?
Oh, I-I'm sorry,
Galileo drank Diet Sprite.
Look, you're my best friend,
she's my girlfriend;
you should bond.
You know,
like you and my mom did.
Your mom creeps
the hell out of me.
Yes, but she's stopped
calling you Slumdog Millionaire.
I do appreciate that.
Here we go.
I'd like to propose a toast.
To science and friendship.
Hold on. Wait.
No, it's okay, go ahead.
What?
Oh, I was working with
penicillin-resistant gonorrhea
in the lab today
and I was just trying to
remember if I washed my hands.
Thanks for the steak, Wyatt.
My pleasure.
It's nice to have dinner
with a boyfriend of Penny's
that knows how to use a napkin.
So not funny, Dad.
Let me tell you about this one
genius she was going out with,
this-this
fella Donnie.
Oh, will you please let it go?
Donnie was gonna make millions
turning farm waste
into biofuel and selling it
to the government.
A lot of people are doing that.
Oh, see?
Yeah, but all Donnie did was mix
pig poop with a little water
and pump it
into his mom's Camry.
Yeah, that's great.
It's a funny story. Moving on.
And Donnie was a rocket
scientist compared to that boy
who wanted to get beer pong
into the Olympics.
What was his
name, sweetheart?
Curtis, and I'm pretty sure
he was joking.
I don't know.
That petition
looked real to me.
Yeah, okay, I think this ends
the ex-boyfriend portion
of our evening.
Well, I'm just glad you finally
found yourself a keeper.
Thanks, Wyatt.
I'm a keeper.
Leonard, you want to come in
for a nightcap?
Oh, gee, Dad,
he'd love to,
but Leonard has to work
in the morning.
Maybe I could
go in a little late.
No, no, no, you can't.
Your career is
far too important.
Behind every great man
is a nagging woman
who won't let him have any fun,
am I right, Leonard?
Don't I know it.
Well, good night, son.
Good night, Wyatt.
Oh, good
night, honey.
Good night.
I love you.
Love you, too.
Oh, friggety-frak.
Not this again.
Three, four, five--
pass go, get 2,000 rupees--
six, seven.
Whoops. Can't go any further.
There's a sacred cow in my way.
Bernadette, please
tell your boyfriend
to cool it with
the cow jokes.
It won't help.
Once he finds a joke he likes,
he sticks with it.
Yeah.
Like his haircut material.
Oh, right.
Did you get your hair cut?
"No. I got them all cut."
Which is still
so funny.
And when you go
to a Chinese restaurant,
he always gets the same fortune
in his fortune cookie.
Right. "Help, I'm a prisoner
in a Chinese
fortune cookie factory."
Okay, I think that's enough
about me.
He's right. Let's make
fun of his mother.
"Howard, come rub my feet!
My corns are killing me!"
"Howard, help me
out of the tub!
I'm stuck again!"
Coming.
Hey, lovebug.
Shut up.
You know what I've been doing
for the last hour?
Mm, dreamily doodling
"Mrs. Leonard Hofstadter"
in a notebook?
Listening to my father
go on and on
about what a great guy you are.
You got to admit,
I am... I'm delightful.
Why are you making this
so difficult?
It's not difficult for me.
I'm having fun.
Leonard.
What do you want me to do?
You started this.
Do you want to go over
and tell him we're broken up?
No.
Well, then, what do you want?
I don't know.
Don't you think that's something
you should
have figured out
before you stomped over here?
Maybe.
Leonard, Penny, excellent.
I'd like to say I'm very happy
that you're back together,
and if I can figure out
a way to do so
and sound sincere, I will.
In the meantime,
I'd like to go over
some proposed changes
to the roommate agreement
specifically to address
Penny's annoying
personal habits.
Oh, my God.
What personal habits?
I have a list.
FYI, overuse of the phrase
"Oh, my God" is number 12.
Okay, Sheldon,
you don't have to do this
because Leonard and I are not...
Ba-ba-ba-ba.
Are you sure you want
to include him in this?
Include me in what?
Is there a plot afoot?
I'll have no
truck with plots.
No, you're right.
No, there's... there's no plots,
no trucks, no feet.
So what other annoying habits
shall we discuss?
Uh, we don't
discuss anything.
Leonard is the signatory
to the roommate agreement.
As such, he bears
responsibility
for all your infractions
and must pay all fines.
Fines?
Yes.
If Penny's going to be
spending nights here again,
you'll need to set up
an escrow account.
Sign here.
Hello, Hawaii.
This is Dr. Koothrappali
in Pasadena.
I'd like you to reposition
the telescope, please.
Scarlett Johansson's house!
I'm kidding, Hawaii.
Mahalo.
Whoo!
It might have
been a mistake
to open that second
bottle of wine.
Well, live and learn.
So, Raj, do you think this
planet you're looking for
could have an atmosphere
that supports life?
Maybe.
If it did, I'd be famous.
I'd be on the cover
of magazines.
And then,
instead of living alone
in my tiny apartment,
I'd have a big mansion.
That sounds great.
It is.
If you like wandering
around a big, empty house
with no one to love you.
We'd come visit you.
No, you wouldn't.
You'd be intimidated
by my wealth and fame.
My only friends would be
my genetically engineered
monkey butler
and the little people I hired
to be my living chess set.
He's taking a turn to
the dark side, isn't he?
Hold on.
He could come back.
Oh, what's the point
of everything?
Nope. He's gone.
You know it's been more
than a year
since I've even kissed a girl?
What about that hookup
at Comic-Con you told me about?
Oh, grow up. I was lying.
I lie all the time.
Nobody wants to kiss me.
Oh, you poor, poor thing.
Raj, you have to know
you're a wonderful man.
There are a lot of girls out
there who'll want to kiss you.
Where?
You just have to look.
No!
Well, this was fun.
Oh! I think
I got a nibble.
Oh, be careful.
Give him some line.
Okay, now reel him in.
Oh, look at that baby.
They're really biting, huh?
Yeah. They do that
when you set it on easy.
Oh, that's me.
Hello.
Oh, hi, sweetie.
Yeah, I got up early
and didn't want to wake you,
so I went out for coffee and ran
into Leonard on the way back.
Guess what-- we're fishing.
Yeah. Right here on his couch.
Hey, baby. I love you!
That's Leonard.
Says he loves you.
What?
I see.
The whole thing's
bull squirt, huh?
Well, that's very disappointing.
Bye.
Oh, hey.
There's been something I've
been meaning to tell you.
I can't believe you would
lie to me like that.
Just for the record, I did not
want to be a part of this.
I'll get to you in a minute.
No hurry.
That my own daughter thinks
I don't love her enough
to support her no matter
what choices she makes--
well, that hurts me deeply.
I'm sorry, Daddy...
Let me finish.
Oh.
I thought we were
past the days
when you would try
to pull the wool over my eyes.
Telling me the baggie in your
underwear drawer is potpourri?
And the pee stick
in your bathroom
is to check for diabetes?
You know, I'm sorry.
You're a grown woman,
and I respect your right
to make your own decisions,
but all I ask
is you respect me enough
to be honest about them.
You're right. Look, from now on,
I will tell you the truth.
Thank you. Now, why don't you go
and put some clothes on
and we'll grab a bite to eat
before I head for the airport.
- Now you.
- Daddy, he had nothing to do...
- Keep walking.
- Okay.
Please, please, please
don't give up on her.
What?
I can't go back to the
skateboard idiots,
the white rappers
and all those
sweaty dumb-asses with
their backwards hats.
Gee, I don't know
if it's in the cards, sir.
Then, stack the deck.
Cheat.
Lie. I don't care.
I want grandkids before I die,
and I want them to grow up
in a house without wheels.
I'll give it a shot.
Thank you.
Now I'm going to do something
here to help you along.
Excuse me?
Just don't panic.
Now, get your sorry,
lying ass out of my face
and make sure I
never see it again!
Oh, the reverse psychology
thing.
I see. That's very clever.
Don't yap. Just get out.
I'll friend you on Facebook.
Oh, there you are.
Just so you know,
I was up all night,
but I have finally completed
the Penny-specific section
of the new roommate agreement.
Yeah, well, not necessary.
We broke up again.
Do you even think
about other people, Leonard?
Do you?
- Hey.
- Oh, how'd it go last night?
Oh, you know.
Same old, same old.
Looked through a telescope,
saw some stars.
Big whoop.
Really?
You waited months
for time with that telescope.
What happened?
Why? You writing a book?
I'm going to propose
a hypothesis.
Last night,
Raj accidentally made contact
with an alien civilization
and has been ordered
by the United States government
to keep it a secret.
Nothing happened.
Can we please just
change the subject?
That sounds rehearsed.
We are not alone.
Hey.
Hello.
You get to play with
Raj's big telescope last night?
Whoa.
Where did that come from?
He never touched my telescope.
Way to go shutting up.
I did shut up. Now you shut up.
Fine.
Thank you.
== Sync, corrected by elderman ==
== for www.addic7ed.com ==
I can't believe
you didn't call me this morning.